ALCHEMY OF SOULS
PART 2
She is nowhere to be found.
- Bu-yeon's boat is the only one missing?
- Yes.
Does that mean someone
purposely kidnapped the bride?
Who would do such a thing?
Let us go.
Sure.
I am very happy that you came.
What are you doing?
Are you not going to carry me?
- Can you not walk?
- Of course, I can.
But people will come looking for me.
It would be much faster to cast a spell
and run with me in your arms.
If that is what you are worried about,
do not worry and just walk.
You are the strongest man in Daeho.
Carrying me would be
a piece of cake for you.
I do not want to waste my energy.
Besides, you do not look that light.
That is because I am wearing layers.
It is difficult to walk with this.
Then…
- take it off.
- Here?
Yes, take it off.
I mean…
this does seem
like a pretty deserted place.
I get that you are impatient,
but doing it here seems inappropriate.
Do you not think so?
After all, this is
our first night together.
Unbelievable. Listen.
I was telling you
to take off that impractical robe.
Why in the world…
- would I want to do anything here?
- Right?
I apologize.
I am just really anxious.
I must have gotten ahead of myself.
Hey, wait.
Do not worry.
I am only taking off this robe.
Are you sure you were not locked up
because you hurt your head?
No, but I was ill.
I was on the verge of death,
but my mother found me and treated me.
Why were you ill?
To be frank,
I do not know what it was myself.
Once I regained consciousness,
I was already a lot better.
How could you not know?
You may not remember anything
from when you were unconscious,
but what about before that?
Was it because you got hurt,
or was it an illness?
You see,
I remember nothing before Jinyowon.
I lost all my memories when I was ill.
My condition is the reason
why my mother kept me a secret…
and hidden from everyone.
No one knows of Bu-yeon's existence.
Who could have taken her?
Park Dang-go of Songrim
knew about Jinyowon's wedding ceremony.
Perhaps he thought it was my wedding
and stole the boat carrying the bride,
hoping to ruin the ceremony.
The person from Jinyowon getting married
is Jin Bu-yeon, not Jin Cho-yeon?
Yes.
She and my Uncle Yun-o,
who came with me from Seoho Fortress,
are having the wedding ceremony in secret.
I am only telling you
because you will not stop crying.
Here.
Thank you.
Thank goodness it is not Cho-yeon.
But wait a minute.
Jin Bu-yeon is actually alive?
Have you met her?
- What is she like?
- I have not met her yet.
Uncle Yun-o said he would
introduce her to me after the wedding.
I guess I will know once I meet her.
I was told Jin Bu-yeon was blind,
but you are not.
That is also strange.
Apparently, I was when I was little,
but my sight came back after I recovered.
I remember none of that, though.
- What?
- You do not have it.
I do not have what?
The blue mark of a soul shifter.
The energy sometimes enters the eyes
and enables a blind person to see.
But I guess that was not the case.
I thought they were found
on the left shoulder.
Some have them in their eyes?
Yes.
I have never heard of such a thing.
I am the only one who has seen it.
That makes sense since you are a mage
who hunts down soul shifters.
You must have killed
the infamous soul shifter as well.
What is it? Did you fail to catch her?
- She died.
- "She died"?
Was it not you who killed her?
I guess not.
Did you know her? Were you close?
You ask too many questions.
I told you my story,
so I just wanted to hear yours.
I know I picked you
to be my husband on a whim,
but I would like to get to know you.
You could not stop praising me
when you wanted me,
but are you getting picky
now that I am here?
I just want to know more about you.
Is that so bad?
So you can leave me
if you find me insufficient?
I thought you wanted someone
who could defy your mother
and help you escape.
If it is a loving husband
you are looking for
instead of a means to escape,
then let us say goodbye now.
I will send you back on the boat
to where you were.
No way.
As long as you free me
from that sickening cell,
I will stay with you no matter what.
You can be a thug for all I care.
Fortunately, I am not that bad.
I will still be reasonable. Do not worry.
But…
Why did you come for me?
You obviously are not smitten with me,
and you do not seem to pity me either.
What is it that you need me for?
You told me that
you could see the energy inside me.
What you are seeing
is the ice stone.
Ice stone?
Long ago, Jin Bu-yeon found the ice stone
that was lying at the bottom
of Lake Gyeongcheondaeho.
- Me?
- You do not need to remember.
I just need your great divine powers.
That is why I need you.
My divine powers?
It is the ice stone.
He possesses the ice stone.
They say Jang Uk is
always followed by wraiths and grotesques.
That must be why every time I meet him,
it sends a shiver down my spine.
Then do not listen to Master Lee
and stop visiting him.
He still bothers me, though.
I get curious
about how he is doing as well.
Jang Uk cannot use that power
for his own personal use.
If he ever does,
Park Jin will have to give up his life.
He gave his word to the royal family
and Unanimous Assembly
as he stepped down
from the leader position.
And I have you to thank
for helping me keep Jang Uk
in the palm of my hand.
I am grateful for your acknowledgment.
Just think of Jang Uk as a tool
that helps you utilize
the energy of the sky.
Did Jin Mu tell you
to think that of me
to make you feel better?
Uncle Yun-o.
Were you not supposed
to get married tonight?
I could not.
Someone stole my bride.
Park Dang-go,
the newly appointed leader of Songrim,
thought I was marrying Jin Cho-yeon
and kidnapped the bride.
I…
did what?
I am here to retrieve
what Park Dang-go has stolen from me.
Find and bring him here this instant.
What exactly
did our leader steal from Jinyowon?
You cannot just come here
in the middle of the night
and demand what you want.
Have you no manners?
If you do not cooperate,
I will find him myself.
Search all of Songrim
and find Park Dang-go.
Lady Jin.
Lord Dang-go is here.
Lady Jin, do not be mistaken.
It was not me.
I did not kidnap the bride
on her way to the wedding.
"Wedding"?
"Bride"?
You knew about Jinyowon's wedding ceremony
and went around asking about it,
did you not?
Yes, that I did.
I thought it was for Young Lady Jin.
Although I wanted to ruin the ceremony,
I did not.
Dang-go was with me all night.
He was not the person…
who kidnapped Jin Bu-yeon.
Are you saying you came here
looking for your eldest daughter,
Jin Bu-yeon?
My goodness, this is so confusing.
What is this about Jin Bu-yeon?
That girl is dead!
Cho-yeon.
Explain to me what is going on.
Well, the thing is…
My sister is alive.
She has been living in Jinyowon
for the last three years.
What? She is alive?
Yes, that is right.
I came here looking for Bu-yeon.
She disappeared today
during her wedding ceremony.
I was too flustered
having lost my precious daughter.
I apologize for the discourtesy.
I will be off now.
Jin Bu-yeon.
So you are alive.
Why was Young Lady Jin so angry?
She probably felt embarrassed and upset
when she found out it was not you.
You thought she was getting married,
but all you did was drink.
She has the right to feel angry.
I am the leader of Songrim now.
I can no longer do whatever I want,
so I held back.
What would you have done?
If I were you…
I would have done it.
Because now I know
how much I will regret it…
if I decide to walk away.
When I found out it was her,
I should have stepped forward
and held onto her
instead of stepping away.
Dang-go.
The most tragic experience
is to live your entire life
regretting what you could have done.
Please do not live that way.
Young Master, you are back.
Yes.
Go on inside.
What a nice place.
It looks larger than Jinyowon.
What now?
Are you calculating
how wealthy your husband must be?
Jinyowon is extremely rich too.
Marrying a girl from a rich family like me
will help you boost your wealth.
Not interested.
All I need is your great divine powers.
What about other qualities?
I might have more to offer.
No.
That is the only reason I need you.
But that is the one thing
I do not possess.
Gosh, I should not have said
my powers were that great.
Young Master Jang,
where in the world were you?
Oh, hey…
Who, may I ask, are you?
- I am...
- My bride-to-be.
Pardon? Your bride-to-be?
It is so sudden...
Maidservant Kim, I will explain later.
Our guest is very exhausted right now.
Could you prepare a room for her?
Please, Maidservant Kim.
Yes, Young Master.
I will find a room for her to rest in.
Maidservant Kim raised me
ever since I was a baby.
She is very dear to me,
so please treat her with respect.
She is kind at heart,
so she will make you feel at home.
You asked a person that dear to you
to look after me?
- What about it?
- It is just…
I thought you would give me a hard time
for forcing you to take me with you.
I did not expect you to be so hospitable.
Who says I was forced?
I know I was not the most welcoming,
but I went there because I needed you.
You are my betrothed now,
so you should be treated accordingly.
But people will be suspicious
about you bringing me here.
Should we not be careful?
I thought
you came with me because you were fed up
with being locked up.
There is nothing to be careful of.
Just do as you wish.
No one here
will stop you from doing what you want.
Thank you for saying that.
I will try my best to feel at home.
I will accept your hospitality.
You will find this room
the most comfortable.
I will quickly bring you some food.
I hope it suits your palate.
Let me know if you need anything.
I will.
When you are done bathing,
I will have clean clothes ready for you.
I did not have time
to get you anything new,
so I brought you clothes that
used to belong to Madam Do-hwa.
It looks nice on you.
It is not only pretty,
but it is also light and comfortable.
By any chance,
is it all right if I keep this?
It is neither in trend nor is it new.
But if you like it, go ahead.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
You see…
I am acquainted with a lot of people.
So I know every young lady
that lives in the capital.
But I have never seen you before.
I have never left my house.
That is probably why.
I see.
Your parents must be very strict.
Where are the young master's parents?
Do they not live here?
They both passed away.
Did you not know?
We only just met.
By any chance,
do you also not know
what happened to him three years ago?
So you know nothing about him,
yet you followed him here
just because he asked you to marry him?
I was the one who asked.
I asked him to marry me.
It was me who asked.
And he said yes to that?
Yes.
How strange.
I never thought
he would even consider
getting married again.
This is hard to believe.
I wonder what he is thinking.
Jin Bu-yeon had divine powers
that were as powerful as Jin Seol-ran's.
Do you wish to remove the ice stone?
If you do that, you will die.
Are you all right?
What happened?
Why are you soaked in water?
Look.
Excuse me.
Are you all right?
Are you awake?
Where am I?
How did I end up here?
I must find the ice stone.
I was told I would find him in his study.
What are you doing?
Are you stealing that?
I am sorry.
I am just so used
to stealing food and drinks.
Leave it here.
What?
You said it was all right
to do as I wished.
I always stole alcohol and drank alone.
Have a drink with me
to celebrate my escape.
If you drink that,
it means we are officially married.
Let us think of it as a wedding drink.
Go on. Drink up.
A wedding drink?
Drink up.
Why are you not drinking it?
There is no need to rush
our first night together.
Take it slow. The night is young.
Summer nights are shorter.
The sun will shine any time now.
What does that have anything to do
with becoming a married couple?
I prefer it when it is dark.
It would be awkward to do it in daylight.
You really have a way
of surprising me with your words.
Drinking during the day is bad for you.
I only drank stolen alcohol at night,
so go on.
Drink up.
Fine.
I will drink as soon as I check something.
This is our first night together.
You said it makes you feel awkward.
Here.
You can turn off the last lantern.
For your information,
I received this as a gift from Jinyowon
for complicated reasons.
They said it was some kind of a lantern
that never turns off.
Anyway, the light cannot be blown out.
Since you are
a great priestess of Jinyowon,
use your divine powers to turn it off.
I am waiting.
You cannot do it.
Why can you not do it?
I thought you had great divine powers.
Apparently, I lost my divine powers
along with my memory.
All I can do is see energy with my eyes.
Nothing else.
Then you are of no use to me.
Go home at daybreak.
Tell them you got lost.
You said you escaped a few times.
Do you know why I got caught
every time I ran away?
Because of this.
They always used this to find me.
The tracking thread found
the bride's boat.
Follow the energy of the tracking thread,
and we will find her.
The thread is tightening around my wrist.
That means they will be here soon.
So this is how they find you.
People from Jinyowon will come,
and they will know it was you who took me.
When they come…
I will tell them that
we got married overnight.
This means
I cannot send you back quietly.
This thread comes from Jinyowon,
and no sword is strong enough to cut it.
Jang Uk.
I do not wish to go back.
I like it here.
And I like you too.
I cannot feel the energy
of the tracking thread.
The thread has been cut.
There.
I cut the thread.
Now you can quietly return home.
Leave once the sun rises.
I will leave now.
It will be more embarrassing
to be caught in broad daylight.
I may have deceived you,
but not everything was a lie.
I do have great divine powers.
And the person who treated me told me
that once I get my memory back,
my divine powers will come back as well.
I am sorry I lied to you.
Thank you for your hospitality.
When I get back,
I will not mention your name.
Bu-yeon has disappeared.
Do you think
she has regained her memories and powers?
If she regained her memories,
she may have run away.
After all, the soul inside that body
belongs to Naksu.
The body is Bu-yeon's.
The blood of the eldest daughter
of the Jin family runs in that body.
Is that the reason you confined her
and tried to marry her off
to carry on the family line?
What were you planning to do with her body
once she gave birth to a baby?
Get rid of it once again?
Did you forget what you promised me
when you begged me to save her life
after you found her body
at the bottom of Lake Gyeongcheondaeho?
The body has petrified
without a single ounce of water left,
yet she is still alive. How miraculous.
3 YEARS AGO
Please save her.
She is my long-lost daughter.
I always wondered why she never ran wild
even with Naksu's energy.
I guess it was because the body
belonged to a Jinyowon priestess.
Naksu did not take over this body
using the alchemy of souls.
Her soul was actually locked up
inside this body.
She called me "Mother."
Bu-yeon's soul
also remains inside this body.
The choice is yours.
The only way to keep this body alive
is to use Naksu's energy
that remains inside the body.
Bu-yeon's soul is clinging to that energy.
In order to use Naksu's energy,
we must get rid of Bu-yeon's soul
while leaving Naksu's.
Are you asking me
to choose Naksu's soul
over my own daughter's?
That or let them both die.
What will you do?
Do you wish to keep the body alive
through Naksu's soul?
Or will you keep your daughter's soul
and watch her die?
I will respect your decision.
She is recovering using Naksu's energy.
As the energy flows in her face
and she starts looking human again,
her features will
slowly resemble those of Naksu's.
The body and soul must be one
for her not to run wild.
Are you telling me to look at that face
and think of her as my daughter?
You made your own choice.
You decided to use all of Naksu's energy
to save your daughter's body.
She has a new body now,
so her memory is gone.
Naksu's soul may still remain,
but she lost both her energy
and memory.
She remembers nothing,
which is why she thinks you are her mother
and does not struggle to accept
that she is Jin Bu-yeon.
She opens the doors to Jinyowon
and sees the energy of the world
because my daughter's blood
runs inside her.
But she has no other powers.
My daughter
used to handle relics inside Jinyowon
as if they were her toys.
Does this mean she lost her divine powers?
Bu-yeon's body has no divine powers,
and Naksu's soul has no memory,
so the body and soul do not conflict.
If she regains her divine powers,
Naksu's memory will likely follow.
Can you bear that?
I would rather have her stay that way
than have Naksu's memory come back.
Then are you going to keep her confined?
That is my decision to make.
And if I decide to kill her
because I can no longer stand it,
then so be it.
You promised to respect my decisions.
Jang Uk loved her.
If you tell him,
he will help you protect her.
No. He was in love with Naksu.
She will only live
as my daughter, Bu-yeon.
I will not let him find out about her.
Besides, Jang Uk does not know
what Naksu's real face even looks like.
Even if the two ever do meet,
they will not be able
to recognize each other.
I have to live my life in agony
looking at that girl's face,
so that is the price that must be paid.
I respected your decision as a mother
and did not tell anyone
about her existence.
However, today…
the entire world ended up
finding out about Bu-yeon.
What is important is that I find her.
She has escaped a few times before,
but I always managed to find her.
This time…
it will be no different.
Goodbye, my lady.
What is that smell?
Is it the smell of water?
What is that?
I sense a strange kind of energy.
Are you on patrol?
Did something happen?
Mister. Wake up.
I am sure it came in here.
Hey, wake up. Are you all right?
It is not inside him.
Where did that energy go?
I know you are hiding in there.
Why did you come here?
This may be broken,
but it is a Jinyowon relic
that still holds power.
Eat this and go away.
Young Master.
Did something strange
enter the house again?
Should I wake Maidservant Kim?
I already took care of it.
Just let her sleep.
You will get cold tonight
because you came in contact with it.
Drink some strong liquor
before going to bed.
Yes, Young Master.
She came to check up on me
and tried to help me.
She will also be feeling cold.
I will bring a brazier
and some strong liquor.
If you drink that,
it means we are officially married.
Let us think of it as a wedding drink.
She is of no use to me,
and yet she is a nuisance.
Here is the portrait I received
before the wedding.
Can you really find her?
With the help
of Songrim's merchants' association,
every person in Daeho
will get to see this portrait by today.
I will help Young Lady Jin
find her sister.
WHOEVER FINDS THIS LADY
WILL BE REWARDED GENEROUSLY
She is Jin Bu-yeon,
the eldest daughter of Jinyowon.
All the ladies at Jinyowon are beautiful.
Is it true that
whoever finds her will be rewarded?
Yes, it says it right there.
Goodness, they are giving a reward.
Does that mean Jin Bu-yeon is going to be
the next leader of Jinyowon?
Most likely.
Ever since she was young,
she was known for her great divine powers.
Lady Jin's divine powers have weakened,
so many have been saying
the Jin family should no longer be
in charge of the relics and artifacts.
So this is good news for the Jin family.
Are you saying the Seo family
and the Jin family were
planning to become in-laws?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Yun-o, we are cousins.
How could you not tell me
about the wedding?
I cannot believe even my own family
would disrespect me like this
because of how I look.
No one in the family knows.
Lady Jin insisted
the wedding be held in secret.
Please do not be angry.
Then I guess Lady Jin
also has no respect for me.
Her dead husband is the reason
why I look like this.
Wait a minute.
You were going to marry into the family
that did this to me?
Forgive me.
The marriage has been canceled.
Please calm down.
Not a single person
acknowledges the pain I feel.
Could you please
help me find a way
to get out of this body?
There is no other way.
I cannot let you shift souls
just because you are the Queen.
Anyway, now that we know
that Jinyowon's heir is alive and well,
they can appoint her as the official heir
at the Unanimous Assembly.
Are you telling me
that this is the face of Jin Bu-yeon?
Yes.
Even Songrim is helping them find her,
so it must be true.
This is Naksu's face.
I do not know about anyone else,
but her face is one I cannot forget.
So…
how can she be Jin Bu-yeon?
I should look into it.
She is Jin Bu-yeon?
That is not her.
Jin Bu-yeon is Mu-deok.
You must keep your body warm.
Mr. Lee told me what happened last night.
Thank goodness you are all right.
I am sorry for worrying you.
By the way,
I heard you were
going to leave last night.
Did Young Master Jang not say anything?
He stayed by your side all night.
Then he told me
to give you some medicine for the chills
and just left.
I am about to go to Sejukwon
to get some medicine for you.
Maidservant Kim.
How many days' worth did he ask for?
He asked for three days' worth.
Three days' worth?
Then I guess I will be staying here
for at least three days.
I bet you were
awfully startled last night.
Young Master Jang is
always surrounded by wicked things…
which is why he is never able
to sleep properly.
Why does that happen to him?
It is because of
the great power within him.
They are drawn to it
like moths to a flame.
Did he need my divine powers
to get rid of that?
He asked if I could
take out the ice stone.
Will he find peace
if that gets taken out?
My lord.
What are you doing today?
They are red beans.
Are you making red bean porridge?
I am going to make meju with red beans.
You are going to make meju
with red beans, not soybeans?
"Making meju with red beans"
is an expression
that people use
to describe a lie or bluff.
But if I actually make meju
with red beans,
then that expression will no longer exist.
Everyone thinks this is impossible,
and I will be the first
to prove them wrong.
I am going to challenge myself.
I bet you will lose.
Meju is made with soybeans.
- Red beans might work.
- Soybeans.
- Red beans.
- Soy.
- Red.
- Soybeans.
- Red beans.
- Red.
- Soy.
- Red beans.
- Red…
-Soy…
-Soy, red…
You and I really do click well.
Goodness.
Even if you do make meju with red beans,
I will not even be that shocked.
Something even more shocking
happened last night.
What?
Young Master Jang
suddenly brought a lady home,
saying he will marry her.
Uk wants to marry someone?
This is more shocking
than what you are about to do, right?
Uk is still not over that girl, right?
Of course not.
She is still…
in his heart.
My lord.
I really do hope you succeed
in making meju with red beans.
Show me that impossible things
sometimes do happen.
Uk brought someone home
saying he will marry her?
Three days of taking medicine.
A man and a woman
living together for three days?
That is pretty much a married couple.
There is still hope.
Who are you?
I am Young Master Jang's physician.
I came because I heard Maidservant Kim
dropped by for some medicine.
I guess he sent you to take care of me,
although it was not necessary.
Who exactly are you?
Young Lady Heo.
She looks exactly like the lady
that Lord Dang-go
and Young Master Seo Yul are looking for.
You are right.
Is your name Jin Bu-yeon?
How do you know my name?
No one knows who I am.
What are you talking about?
Your face is all over the capital.
Everyone is looking for you.
What are you doing
at Young Master Jang's place?
- You should get out of here.
- Sun-i.
Everyone knows about me,
and people are looking for me?
Mother would never do that.
Then who is looking for me?
Are those your clothes?
Is that not a wedding dress?
Did you say a man named Seo Yul
is looking for me?
Pardon?
Yes.
A man from the Seo family
at Seoho Fortress?
The man who lacks nothing? Is that him?
Yes, pretty much.
Why do you think Jin Bu-yeon was here?
I do not know.
Where are you going this time?
I am leaving.
Tell Uk that I do not need the medicine.
Pardon?
Seo Yul really is looking for me.
He is looking for me
even though I ran away on our wedding day?
I am guessing he went against my mother
seeing that he revealed
my face to the world.
It will not be a bad idea
to bet my life on him.
I had no idea you were from Jinyowon.
I apologize for not recognizing you
and calling you a thief.
Everyone is looking for you.
Shall I escort you back to Jinyowon?
First, I would like to meet Seo Yul.
Is he here?
Young Master Seo is…
Let me see if he is in his room.
Please wait.
Let me meet him first.
If he turns out to be all right,
I will choose him.
Does that count
as a wedding drink?
You should never date a man with a past
as painful as a stab to the heart.
A past as painful as a stab to the heart?
He must be in a lot of pain.
Young Lady.
Young Master Seo is coming right this way.
Everyone is looking for you,
but I never thought
you would come looking for me.
I apologize for running away
on the day of the wedding.
Now that I have met you,
I regret having done that.
If I had met you first,
I would not have hesitated
about getting married.
Why would I have affected your decision?
Because you are handsome.
It is only natural to waver
when one meets a handsome man.
But that is as far as I can go.
Last night, I already gave my heart
to someone else.
I thought I packed all my clothes
and brought everything with me,
but last night's memory still lingers
and will not allow me to move on.
Are you saying you no longer wish to marry
a member of the Seo family?
Yes.
So I would appreciate it
if you would stop the public search.
All right.
I will relay the message to my uncle.
I was not your betrothed.
A man with the surname Seo
from Seoho Fortress.
- You came on a boat.
- I came with my uncle.
I guess you misunderstood
because you did not know his name.
So it was not you?
Thank goodness.
Now it is a lot easier
to give up the marriage.
To be honest,
I was worried that I might regret it.
But now I feel fine.
What is the matter?
Have we ever met before?
That is impossible.
I never went outside.
I need to go. I have three days' worth
of medicine waiting for me.
Please let your uncle know.
It is time to go back, my lady.
Could you just give me a bit more time?
Just three days.
Then I will willingly enter that room
and stay there, just as Mother wants.
Just give me three days.
I am here on Lady Jin's orders.
Come with us.
Was she confined?
Young Master.
Was that lady from Jinyowon?
The entire capital is looking for her.
Maybe that is why, but she suddenly left.
- She left?
- Yes.
She took her wedding dress and everything.
What happened?
What matters is that she is gone.
Forget about yesterday.
I knew it.
Some things are just impossible.
Now that it is broken,
you can go anywhere you want, right?
If you wish to run, I can help.
If you want, I can give you some money.
You promised not to say my name,
so think of it as a settlement.
My mother…
lost me when I was little
and looked for me for over ten years.
I do wish to come out
because it gets suffocating inside,
but I cannot just plainly disappear.
If I do that,
she will lose her daughter again.
And that will kill her inside.
I cannot do that to her.
I guess she went back
and got locked up again.
My precious daughter.
I thought I lost you again.
I am sorry, Mother.
My sweetheart.
Bu-yeon.
My daughter.
You broke off the engagement?
The Queen is not happy with it.
I did not think that far ahead.
Then what will happen to her?
Why should I care?
They kept her hidden
because they were embarrassed by her.
I did them a favor
by offering to marry her.
But they ruined everything.
Is it happening again?
You came to Daeho
because the pain worsened.
Did you ask Master Heo to treat you?
Please do not tell anyone
about my condition.
His Majesty has ordered you
to bring Jin Bu-yeon
to the Unanimous Assembly.
Since when did the royal family
give orders to mages
regarding the Unanimous Assembly?
Did you advise them to do that
as the Gwanju of Cheonbugwan?
Just let me meet her.
I saw a portrait of her,
but I would like to meet her in person.
Why do you…
want to see her?
I am still her uncle.
It is only natural
that I want to meet my long-lost niece.
She is a beautiful girl.
Master Lee tells me
that she takes after me.
Master Lee? The pupil of Seo Gyeong?
Yes.
When we found Bu-yeon,
she was extremely ill.
Master Lee treated her
and looked after her.
Thanks to you,
I once humiliated myself
by welcoming a fake daughter.
I received Master Lee's help
to prevent that from happening again.
If he confirmed it for you,
then it must be Bu-yeon without a doubt.
But why did you keep her hidden?
I told you she was ill.
Is she well now?
The Unanimous Assembly will suggest
that Jinyowon's relics and artifacts
be moved elsewhere.
It means the duty to protect Jinyowon
could get passed on
to a different family.
That is nonsense.
This is what happens when you keep
your doors closed for three years.
The leader of Jinyowon is old,
which means her power
is weakening day by day.
Meanwhile, she has no heir
with strong divine powers.
Why would anyone think it would be safe
to leave the Jin family in charge
of all those dangerous
and valuable relics and artifacts?
Is that the advice
you are giving me
as the Gwanju of Cheonbugwan?
Here is my advice to you as your brother.
Bring Bu-yeon to the Unanimous Assembly.
She is known to have divine powers
as powerful as Jin Seol-ran's.
If you announce her as your official heir,
then you will be able to keep Jinyowon.
All right, then.
I will see you at the Unanimous Assembly.
Jin Bu-yeon is going to attend
the Unanimous Assembly
held at Cheonbugwan.
Jin Bu-yeon has been
the talk of the town for a while now.
I guess she is finally showing up.
Would you like to attend?
No.
I do not have fond memories of her.
The last time I went to see her,
I ended up trapped inside a barrier.
You are right.
Goodness.
It was so foggy that I could not see.
- Right.
- It rained too.
Gosh.
I tried to make meju with red beans,
but I failed.
So I used it to make red bean porridge.
How does it taste?
You say you failed,
but it somehow tastes like meju.
It does, right?
I really think
I might be able to turn it into meju.
Did you invite me to eat
what you failed to make?
Uk.
I heard you brought home
someone you wished to marry.
I figured Maidservant Kim would tell you.
Why did you kidnap
the priestess of Jinyowon
on the day of her wedding?
She was pretty.
I was mesmerized by her beauty.
Were you going to ask
that beautiful woman
to take out the ice stone for you?
You punk.
You should marry someone
you wish to spend your life with,
not someone who will take your life away.
Do not worry. She ran away.
Good.
I heard she is going to be announced
as the official heir of Jinyowon tonight.
Jin Bu-yeon? How?
She is a priestess
with great divine powers.
It seems like there have been concerns
regarding Jinyowon.
If her eldest daughter attends
the Unanimous Assembly
and gets announced as the heir,
Jinyowon will be able to show
that they still stand strong.
So they are trying to make meju
with red beans.
Do you know how you can succeed
in making meju with red beans?
Is there really a way?
First, you hide it.
Then you make sure no one tastes it.
Does it taste that bad?
Yes.
It tastes
absolutely horrible.
I will bring you some honey.
Then it will be sweet red bean porridge.
Red beans can never turn into meju.
How foolish of her.
She should have run away.
I did not want to take you there,
but that is the only way
to protect Jinyowon.
Mother.
I have no power.
Will it be all right?
That is why
you must help me.
Bu-yeon, you must never
leave this place again.
You cannot ever see anyone
now that everyone knows you.
We cannot let anyone find out
that the heir of Jinyowon
has no divine powers.
Then I will have to stay…
in this room forever.
Please do it for me.
Your tracking thread has snapped off.
Let us tie it so that it can never
break off again.
How…
did that turn off?
Apparently, I lost my divine powers
along with my memory.
She clearly told me
that she could not turn it off.
I may have deceived you,
but not everything was a lie.
Is it true that Jin Bu-yeon has
immense divine powers?
She found the ice stone, did she not?
If she really does show up today,
the Jin family can continue
to be in charge of protecting Jinyowon
without any concerns.
After today's assembly, you will go home
and do as you promised.
You will never step outside
of Jinyowon ever again.
Is that Jin Bu-yeon?
I would like to introduce to you
the heir of Jinyowon.
Hello, everyone.
I am Jin Bu-yeon, the eldest daughter
of the Jin family.
- What happened?
- What is going on?
- What?
- What is it?
- What is this?
- What is happening?
Jang Uk?
What is Jang Uk doing
at the Unanimous Assembly?
You left without taking your medicine.
Everyone was looking for me.
Why are you here?
To check something.
This was turned off.
Did you do it?
I turned it on again.
Try turning it off again.
I…
do not know how.
If you turn this off,
I will take you with me.
Wait…
It turned off.
Did…
Did I do that?
What are you doing?
Jin Bu-yeon…
cannot become the heir of Jinyowon.
What do you think you are doing?
Jin Bu-yeon
is already married to Jang Uk,
the son of the Jang family.
- They got married?
- Married?
- Jin Bu-yeon and Jang Uk?
- What is he saying?
Bu-yeon, what is this nonsense?
He is right, Mother.
This man and I shared a wedding drink
and became husband and wife.
I will not return…
to that room in Jinyowon.
We are married.
Please give us your blessings.
ALCHEMY OF SOULS
PART 2
If my powers can be
considered justification,
I would like to see you
try arguing with that.
I was hoping for this.
Why? What is it?
I need to find out more about Jin Bu-yeon.
I think we have been circling
the same path.
There is nothing wrong
with being air headed.
I was simply flustered.
That looks delicious.
Eunuch, do you have some money?
Me? Were you referring to me?
I shall summon Naksu's soul once again
to distract Jang Uk.
Subtitle translation by: Joy Lee