What an insane thing to do!
Is killing and bringing one
back to life entertaining to watch?
We cannot even intervene
because Mu-deok foolishly agreed to it.
That girl…
smiled.
Yes. I will try it.
She only said yes
because of the gold she would be getting.
Could gold really be the reason…
why she smiled?
I am not happy
about this situation either.
I will make sure you die a painless death.
This is not to see me die.
It is to see me come back to life.
They will try to buy time with that book
and look for a way to expose you.
When she dies
and the ice stone's power is summoned,
use the ice stone's power
to shift your soul into that girl's body.
The Unanimous Assembly will come
to an end once the Queen dies.
We will safely leave Songrim
with the ice stone.
I wonder why His Majesty
chose her of all people.
She is the weakest one among us.
He picked the right person.
You look beautiful.
My Bu-yeon.
Mother.
No one is looking at you right now.
Use that power to shift souls.
It is not me.
I am not the one controlling
the ice stone.
Then who?
You need to stop that.
Mother, are you all right?
Bu-yeon.
Did she recognize her? This is not good.
They are going to bring her back to life.
That cannot happen.
She needs to die.
What is going on?
Where is the ice stone?
What just happened?
Did you see that?
The power of the ice stone
and the power of the sky came together.
The heavens must have taken the ice stone
and made it disappear.
It did not disappear.
It is
still here.
Where exactly is it?
Lightning, thunder, and now fog
in broad daylight?
That is not all.
Something has gone awry.
- The cloth covering the ice stone, right?
- Yes.
Could something have happened to it?
Is this a dream or something?
- There are flowers everywhere.
- This feels surreal.
Are we dead?
- Are we in utopia?
- Hey.
Do not speak nonsense.
Then would that make me the Jade Emperor,
and him a fairy?
A fairy.
What is that?
I do not think it is a fairy.
Then is it a ghost?
Are you mages?
Yes, we are from Jeongjingak.
You were here too, Young Lady Heo.
Please let go of me.
Jang Uk, remain here and stand guard.
You three.
Patrol the area.
- I will head to the Training Center.
- Your Royal Highness, we will escort you.
What is going on?
I heard deafening thunder.
We do not know yet either.
We will find out soon once this fog lifts.
If we are not in utopia or the afterlife,
where did all these flowers come from?
Is this even a real fog?
What are you doing?
We do not know what happened.
The moment we reached the gate,
a strong gust of wind hit us.
Wind?
There is no wind.
Do not go there. We cannot see it,
but there is great energy blocking us.
What in the world is going on?
It is a barrier.
I believe there is a barrier
around Jeongjingak.
A barrier?
Who would place a barrier here?
Your Royal Highness.
A priestess from Jinyowon
is inside Jeongjingak.
Jin Bu-yeon,
who had brought the ice stone,
was found collapsed in the building.
Mu-deok.
The ice stone's energy entered Jeongjingak
and created a barrier.
Who is inside Jeongjingak?
Jang Uk and Seo Yul
are nowhere to be seen.
They must be in there.
Young Lady Heo is inside as well.
- My dear Yun-ok!
- The Crown Prince.
He is in there!
- What?
- Was Beom in there as well?
Where is Jin-ho?
Lady Jin.
Do something.
The ice stone swallowed up your daughter,
so she must be in there too.
We cannot be rash.
We all witnessed what happened
after Bu-yeon provoked it.
This is all Jinyowon's fault.
You wanted to see
how powerful the ice stone was.
Why are you placing the blame on us?
Are you trying to pick a fight again?
That is enough. The kids are in there!
Yun-ok!
Do you have anything to do
with the barrier around Jeongjingak?
What happened back at the Training Center?
You see…
It definitely all happened
because of Mu-deok.
After all, she is the real Jin Bu-yeon,
the priestess of Jinyowon.
But everyone thinks I am her.
I cannot say that it was because of her.
What do I do?
Answer me.
I…
Do not know.
I am blind,
so I could not see what had happened.
I fainted when the wind struck
and just woke up.
You do not know how you came here?
I do not even know where I am,
so how am I to know how I came here?
She does not look too well.
The color has drained from her face
and she is sweating.
What do you think?
I think you should let her rest first,
Your Royal Highness.
Let her rest.
Come.
She must be lying.
What is she hiding?
Mu-deok would know.
Mu-deok, you were with her, right?
How did you end up here?
I was here all along.
You were here?
Were you not pouring tea
at the Training Center?
I was, but then
I followed you here immediately.
I do not know what happened back there.
What is the point in asking a maid
who knows nothing
but to follow her master like a puppy?
Do not worry, Your Royal Highness.
The best mages have gathered
for the Unanimous Assembly.
This barrier will be broken in no time.
Bring some tea for the Crown Prince.
Yes, of course.
A puppy who only follows her master.
A maid who knows nothing.
That is Mu-deok.
Look at that.
There is no water to boil.
Spell-brewed tea tastes the best.
It has been a while.
I have finally regained my power
thanks to the ice stone.
What is going on? Where am I?
We did not lose it this time.
We are inside the ice stone.
This is the ice stone?
The ice stone is not limited
in shape, size, or form.
It can be water, fire,
or wind.
Does this mean I have the ice stone now?
No one can truly own the ice stone.
You only use its power.
Pull and get pushed.
Earn one, and lose the other.
That is the burden you will have to carry.
I can gladly endure that.
Then try it.
Overflowing power means
you will not be able to control
how much of it you use.
Desire rain, and you will get a flood.
Desire wind, and you will get a typhoon.
Try to endure it.
What are you?
A relic of Jinyowon?
How dare a soul living off my body
call me a relic?
Jeongjingak?
What was that?
A relic from Jinyowon
that had attached itself to the ice stone?
Mu-deok, what is this?
The Crown Prince's teacup is chipped.
I am sorry.
Let me get a new one.
No. I do not need
to be servile any longer.
- Mu-deok.
- Yes, young master.
The table is dirty. Wipe it clean.
I do not hesitate to be subservient.
Have I become Mu-deok to the bone?
I am no longer Mu-deok.
Mu-deok.
We have not eaten anything all day
due to the Unanimous Assembly.
Do you have any food?
The sujebi we have
as a late-night snack is tasty.
Can you make some?
I will only be Mu-deok
until I make this dish.
After this, I will no longer be her.
Once I can shift souls,
I can choose any body I want.
I could even be the King.
Or should I kill my enemy
and take over his body?
How distasteful.
I would rather choose Park Jin.
I can pick any body I want.
Let me think this through.
This is perfect.
It would be a waste
to make sujebi with this.
Should I make noodles instead?
Uk prefers noodles.
I do get a very faint taste of it.
This will be the last meal
Mu-deok makes for her young master.
- Young Master.
- Yes?
I made some noodles. Go and have some.
Sure.
As your maid, I shall leave you now.
And…
this will be the end, my pupil.
The end?
You probably did not realize it.
But we are inside the ice stone.
I regained my power like I did
back at Lake Gyeongcheondaeho.
I will use this ice stone to shift souls
and leave this body.
Are you saying
you will not ever see me again?
We agreed that it would be the end
once I regained my power.
But we agreed
to talk about our future as well.
There is…
no other future for us.
Earn one, and lose the other.
That is the burden you will have to carry.
If I need to lose you to regain my power,
I will bear it.
- Young Master.
- Yes?
I made some noodles. Go and have some.
- And...
- Mu-deok.
I think the barrier around Jeongjingak
is actually the ice stone.
What?
That is not something
he should have realized.
They said the ice stone
was water, fire, and wind.
I think we are trapped
within a force created by wind.
If we are indeed inside the ice stone,
could there be a way to take the ice stone
without anyone knowing?
I am not sure.
After all, I have reached Chisu.
Could I snatch it
like I did with the Golden Fish?
Your current power cannot hold a candle
to the ice stone.
I wish you had regained your power
like you did at Lake Gyeongcheondaeho.
You would be able to do it.
What if I regained my power
and took the ice stone with me?
If caught, you may even be killed for it.
Are you not afraid?
The fact that you could run away with it
is always a possibility.
And I already told you
that I was going to take responsibility.
However,
I am still a bit afraid.
I am scared that you may break our promise
and abandon me without even looking back.
Master.
Please do not abandon me.
If you do, I will cry a river.
You say such embarrassing things
so openly.
You will regret it when you look back.
I can always say such things
if I endure the embarrassment.
But I can never turn back time
even if I regret something.
Master, endure the embarrassment
and be honest with yourself.
That way, you will not regret anything.
- Jang Uk, I...
- Young Master Jang.
I will be right there.
She has the key
to the room of forbidden books.
Since we are here,
I want to look up some things.
Right, here.
Have it all. Do not let others find out.
Are you looking
for forbidden books regarding sorcery?
Yes, I heard that my father stored
all the sorcery books that he had gotten
from a shaman here.
I want to look for them.
So they were Lord Jang Gang's.
I will help you.
I can do it alone.
You can leave the key with me and go.
My grandfather entrusted me with it.
How can I trust
that you will keep it safe?
You are right. I am not that trustworthy.
You can keep an eye on me.
Attention, everyone.
We have enough spare rooms
and food at Jeongjingak.
So do not worry too much.
Let us remain calm.
All right?
Go to Gisan and summon everyone there.
We deserve some power
from the ice stone as well.
Yes, master.
Summon everyone who can cast spells.
Even children and the elderly.
- Yes, my lord.
Summon all the mages in Cheonbugwan
to Songrim.
A fight could break out
over the ice stone.
We need to be prepared.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Majesty.
You do not look well.
You should go back to the palace.
I must witness it myself.
Since we have the ice stone,
the King's Star will appear as well.
Everyone must be waiting
for Words of the Heart.
Let us hurry.
Master.
Here is Words of the Heart.
That is not the priority right now.
A barrier has been created
around Jeongjingak.
Pardon?
Will I eventually get caught?
Then I will meet my demise.
It is a honey biscuit.
You were barely eating. Please have some.
Thank you.
Were you surprised to find out
that I was the Jin family's daughter?
When we first met,
I hadn't found my parents yet.
This is your umbrella.
I have kept it with me at all times.
I thought you would recognize it
if we met again.
Assistant Gwanju Jin Mu
helped you find your parents?
Yes.
Please do not tell him
that you and I have met in the past.
If my mother hears about it,
she will be heartbroken
by the things I went through.
Please do not tell him.
Everyone who knew her has been killed.
Did she spare me on purpose?
Jin Mu does not know
that we know that girl's true identity.
It will be a great weakness.
He must have killed them all
just to hide her identity.
She will face the same fate eventually.
If the Queen is planning
to shift souls with her,
they brought her here to be killed.
She has no idea
and is doing everything she can.
He is using her.
Just like how he used Naksu.
So-i is a pitiful girl as well.
Young Master.
Did you know
this umbrella fails
to fulfill its purpose?
Look here. It is already torn.
You are right.
I was told to pay a large sum
as it is a high-quality umbrella.
You must have been fooled.
I am quite gullible.
Is that so?
The soul shifter, Master Kang,
has disappeared?
After feeding on her energy,
he walked out on his own.
We could not find him
anywhere in Sejukwon.
Since the Unanimous Assembly
was held near the Training Center,
I doubt he went there.
Things have been disorderly all day long.
We should have spotted him.
There is one place he could hide
without being seen.
Inside the barrier of Jeongjingak.
He could be there.
A soul shifter.
I am with Jin Mu.
I know you.
I saw you shift souls
in the Cheonbugwan Secret Room.
Your soul shifted out of that old body.
We are on the same side. Please spare me.
I need human energy this instant.
I will find someone for you.
Would you not prefer feeding
on a Jeongjingak mage's energy
instead of mine?
Wait here,
and I will lure someone in.
- A mage of Jeongjingak?
- Yes.
Due to a barrier,
no one can leave
or enter Jeongjingak right now.
A barrier?
Young Lady Jin?
What are you doing there?
I was looking for something,
but then I lost the umbrella
that I use for walking.
There it is.
I will spare you.
Go bring more mages.
Yes, right.
Is Seo Yul here
in Jeongjingak as well?
Why do you ask?
He cut me with his sword.
He shall be the first person I kill.
He is
not here.
If you refuse,
I will kill you first.
I will obey.
There is someone here
that I would like to get rid of.
I will bring her here first.
Please kill her.
Your snacks are not tasty.
Even the noodles were bad.
Since I have yet to tell Jang Uk,
I will be Mu-deok for a bit longer.
I am sorry.
Dang-gu stashed away our leader's liquor.
How does it taste?
It is not bad.
I wonder what they are doing outside
- that they still have not resolved this.
- But still,
we are surrounded by flowers,
the weather is wonderful,
and it is full of energy.
This is not that bad either.
Your Royal Highness.
Watching flowers will bore you.
Would you like to watch me
perform Hyeongong?
He has some fancy techniques.
Is that so?
I will take a look.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
What?
- Beom!
- Beom.
Beom, wake up.
- Hey!
- Hey.
Let us carry him. Beom.
Your energy drained out
when you cast spells?
Yes.
I felt my energy draining out.
It felt like
my energy was draining out
like a broken vase.
I examined his core of energy,
and he has lost a lot of energy.
How could I lose my torrent of energy?
Maybe this sword is the problem.
My energy just drained from the sword.
I think the barrier
is causing the problem.
I think it takes the energy you use…
when you cast spells.
We cannot use spells
or unsheathe our swords in here.
Let us keep our swords here.
This is Naksu's sword
that Master Lee had taken from me.
Did you have it?
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
He wanted me to keep it safe.
But Maidservant Kim
did not want it at home.
So I had kept it here.
Keep this with you
and give it to him once he comes.
I cannot leave the house
when I was entrusted with this.
Maidservant Kim.
So tell me.
Did the Unanimous Assembly go smoothly?
Not at all.
All the mages from different families
are headed to Songrim.
Something must have come up.
He will have to show himself
with all the fuss going around.
Will Gwanju Jang Gang really return?
Who are you to come here?
Gwanju.
Who is Assistant Gwanju's right hand
at the moment?
Cho Chung threatened to expose
the truth about Young Master Jang.
I had no choice
but to teach him the alchemy of souls.
Since he has run wild and died,
is this not the end?
I only did what I did
for you and your son.
I have lost my closest friend
as well as my wife to sorcery.
I will get rid
of all remaining Soul Ejectors
and seal the ice stone
in Lake Gyeongcheondaeho.
No.
After all that you have done to master it.
How could you let go of the ice stone?
You cannot do that.
Since you also learned
the alchemy of souls,
I will destroy your energy flow
so you cannot perform sorcery.
Destroy my energy flow?
No, my lord.
Please do not destroy my energy flow.
I swear I will never perform
the alchemy of souls
which you have taught me. I promise!
I should have destroyed his energy flow.
Instead of hiding the ice stone,
I should have come clean
and destroyed the ice stone.
How did he retrieve the ice stone
from Lake Gyeongcheondaeho?
Or did someone help him?
I feel the same.
But there is only one thing
that makes me different.
It is that…
I am a soul shifter.
Hey, Beom.
You can always train again.
He is right. You will be fine.
Cheer up.
The ice stone is draining their energy.
If I shift souls
and take the stone's energy,
will I be taking their energy as well?
Earn one, and lose the other.
That is the burden you will have to carry.
If I want to regain my power,
I will have to take their energy as well.
And if I do that,
they will die.
I will have to take responsibility
for their deaths.
Filthy Mu-deok, what are you doing here?
He will die as well.
It is dangerous here.
If someone like you touches the barrier,
your bones could get crushed.
Step back.
Are you not going to thank me?
I was showing my concern for you.
You had lost your energy back there.
Are you all right?
Is this how you are thanking me?
Worrying about me too?
Not a bad idea.
I am fine.
I am sorry.
For what?
For making terrible noodles and snacks.
You could not eat anything.
Please have some of this instead.
Honey biscuits, Jang Uk's favorite.
Are you sharing some
that you had gotten for him?
Forget it. You can have them.
Look. I know I should take them.
But I have decided
to give them to you instead. All of those.
I have given them to you.
He may not be the nicest man,
but he has been very considerate.
Take this.
I want to thank you
from the bottom of my heart.
- Your heart?
- Yes, Your Royal Highness.
I mean it.
I am always grateful.
If you want to thank me sincerely,
give me something bigger than that.
I would prefer something grander.
Just take this.
This is just the right amount.
You are unbelievable.
You are always impertinent
and barge your way in.
But whenever I reach for you,
you always back away.
The reason why I am not persistent
in trying to hold on to you
is that if you still refuse, I would…
Forget it. I will not accept
if it is only that amount.
I would have felt
less terrible had he taken it.
Fine.
I do not have to feel entirely guilty.
Mu-deok.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Can you go to the mages' quarters for me?
What for?
It is humid here.
Could you bring me a new blanket?
I heard you can get it there.
Yes, Young Lady.
What are you doing?
Trying to keep
the fire in the brazier alive.
Darn it.
Really?
Are you a moron?
Wait.
Did you just call me a moron?
There are countless books here.
You could have burned them all.
I could have cast a spell to control it.
I was simply flustered…
as I cannot do it right now.
Still, you could have
just closed the lid on it.
They say you are a genius.
But you do not know
what to do when flustered.
- You are just a fool.
- Do not bad-mouth me.
I will get upset.
So you do know how to be upset.
You were always so placid like water.
Even water can boil or freeze.
It does not always stay the same.
It is humid due to the fog.
Were you doing this
because your leg was hurting?
You remembered.
I am fine.
Do not worry.
You said you liked pine pollen tea snacks.
But I never got to give you any.
You remembered that as well.
What is the point?
I never got you any.
Then make some for me next time.
There is no next time.
If I shift souls, he will die as well.
Better yet,
teach me the recipe.
Then I can make it myself. Like last time.
Do you remember?
I cherish
all the memories I had in Danhyanggok.
Seo Yul will die.
I was on my way to the quarters
for some blankets.
I will get going then.
Let me do that. Go to Uk.
He has been looking for you.
I just need to be Naksu again.
I had cut ties with him back then.
I will do the same with everyone.
Glaring at it will not break the barrier.
Did you see that?
The stone passed through.
You are right.
Maybe only things
that have liquid cannot pass.
What a strange barrier.
It filters what can and cannot pass.
What kind of barrier is that?
What are the others doing outside?
Despite all the mages out there,
they have yet to break this barrier.
Is it because the ice stone made it?
They are probably too busy
fighting over who gets the ice stone.
Still, they know
that I am trapped in here.
Perhaps you are not that important
to the Queen who has the ice stone.
How could a mother be like that?
Or is she similar to my father?
Fine.
As you all know,
she is not my biological mother.
Just like you and your father.
That is what everyone says.
I will not apologize even if you are hurt.
Then I will not beat around the bush.
If the Queen and Jin Mu
offer the power of the ice stone to you,
can you still get rid of them?
It would be difficult
to decline such grand power.
You are brave.
You need the courage
to be open about your greed.
And you? What will you do
if you had the ice stone?
I will do what Master Seo Gyeong did.
Seo Gyeong?
Do you mean you wish to become
a hero with the fate of the King's Star
by destroying every ice stone
and saving the world from chaos?
I am sure he did
such a thing out of sincerity.
But I believe he saved one stone
to save someone he loved
out of sincerity as well.
You see, that part touches me more.
So that is what he wrote in his book.
It is just a poor excuse
for not being able to let go of the stone.
Who would believe that?
I do.
Because I would do the same.
What?
Stones pass through the barrier.
Send a notice to urge them
to come to your rescue.
Jang Uk.
You are a genius.
Let me see.
- A barrier…
- Uk.
Is there a bigger stone?
They just need to read your message.
You do not need a bigger one.
I need to write in big letters.
Does this one not budge?
- Cheers.
By the way, why did Dang-gu never tell us
about his stash of liquor?
We should drink it all. Drink up.
- Let us drink.
I brought another brazier.
Mu-deok.
Why are you here?
What do you mean?
Young Master Seo went
to get the blankets himself.
Is Seo Yul here in Jeongjingak as well?
He shall be the first person I kill.
Young Master Seo,
you cannot enter this room.
- What is the matter?
- Please go back.
Can you see me?
You see, I…
Young Master Seo!
Young Master Seo! What do I do?
What do I do?
What?
Who are you?
Yul!
Yul.
- Young Master Seo!
- Are you all right?
Yul.
- What happened?
- A soul shifter.
There is a soul shifter.
What?
A soul shifter is here.
He fed on Yun-su and Jin-ho's energy.
Master Kang of Daegangtongun,
a very powerful man, is the soul shifter.
And he was using his energy
to cast spells.
None of us could use spells in here.
So why can he?
This place drains our energy,
but it must be the opposite for them.
What if I regained my power
and took the ice stone with me?
If caught, you may even be killed for it.
Are you not afraid?
I am still a bit afraid.
I am scared that you may break our promise
and abandon me without even looking back.
- Jang Uk, I...
- Young Master Jang.
Where is Mu-deok?
She was with us up until a while ago.
Where did she go?
There was a nuisance roaming around.
If he is not stopped,
they will all die in there.
They are going to die
once I shift souls anyway.
It would be ridiculous to save them.
This is how I will cut ties with them.
I just feel too guilty.
This will be the last time I save them.
Just this once.
You.
- Where have you been?
- I am here, am I not?
Uk…
Jang Uk could die!
No one can beat him here right now.
We cannot all die.
I will lure and trap him
in the secret room.
Once he traps the soul shifter
and himself in the secret room,
Uk will die.
Why?
Why did he go alone?
He said he had to.
He said he was responsible.
- Where are you going?
- To the secret room.
If the door to the secret room is open,
that means Uk died after failing
to lure the soul shifter there.
If it is closed,
he is probably already dead.
There is no use.
You said you would not be persistent
in trying to hold on to me.
You cannot stop me.
So please let me go.
If it is closed,
he is probably already dead.
But I can never turn back time
even if I regret something.
Jang Uk.
You are still alive,
my pupil.
Why did you hide it?
Because…
I wanted you to die.
Then…
why did you come for me?
Because…
I thought you would die.
Since you have unsheathed the sword,
make your decision.
I know you have been avoiding me.
I also know that everyone's lives
are in your hands.
Like you promised,
point your sword at me first.
If you stab me,
then I will die as the one
who released the assassin.
If you withdraw your sword,
I will make you another promise.
Fine.
Make me another promise
just like you said you would.
What human would choose
to give up on such immense power?
To protect what we must…
What if I give it all away?
I am trying to protect as well.
Why is he here?
Jin Bu-yeon's immense divine powers
not only came from her mother,
a member of the Jin family.
Park Jin! You hid the truth,
despite knowing everything.
Then those leaving shall leave,
and those returning shall return.
Young Master. Do what you must.
I will be trying something
not out of stupidity, but out of vigor.
Just as my master has taught me.
- I look quite nice.
- Goodness.
I heard there was a bride
about to get married soon.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim