Master. It is me, Yeom.
You have been meditating
for 100 days as of yesterday.
It is time that you go outside.
Master.
Master…
Master!
-Oh, dear. Poor boy.
-Poor thing.
-Goodness gracious.
-Unbelievable.
-He must have frozen to death.
-It seems like it.
-I feel so sorry for him.
-Poor child.
-Oh, gosh.
-My goodness.
What is going on? What is it?
Oh, dear! The homeless boy has died.
He was just a young boy.
I feel so bad for him.
My goodness, that poor thing.
Master, as you have always wished,
I will give you a quiet farewell.
Goodness, I feel so bad for him.
He seems like an orphan.
Let us hold a funeral for him.
-Yes.
-Let us do that.
Should we cremate him
and sprinkle the ashes
by Lake Gyeongcheondaeho?
-Oh, my goodness!
-My gosh!
Child…
Are you all right?
-What in the world…
-How…
-Where is he going?
-Where are you going?
Stop!
Child.
Did you just tell me to stop?
How foolish of you.
I cannot believe that
you have already burned my body.
What are you talking about?
Had I been a little late,
you would have burned my cane too.
You fool!
You fool.
Master?
I only temporarily
shifted my soul out of my body
to test if I had reached Hwansu
after my 100 days of meditating.
But I noticed that my body was burning,
so I quickly entered another body.
But it is too late.
Are you saying
you are in this child's body?
Is it really you, Master?
That is right.
I am Lee Cheol, your master.
My goodness…
Master.
I am a soul shifter.
Your Majesty.
Did you not summon me today
to find the soul shifter?
I will do just that.
I can
recognize soul shifters.
Is there anyone else
who has seen your face?
This is an umbrella.
You can use this as a cane.
No.
No one else in the capital knows
that I am not blind.
People will think of this
as a fight between thugs.
You should have stopped searching for me.
So-i.
So-i, is that you?
I am Kim from Sari Village.
You have the wrong person.
We rarely ever talked to each other.
He barely knows me.
That man
must be taken care of.
There was no need to kill him.
Once he left for Sari Village,
we would have never met again.
But you did meet.
Sari Village?
Is that where you used to stay?
I lived there to hide.
I lived there for a while
to hide from those thugs.
Is there anyone else from Sari Village
who might recognize you?
I always kept a distance
so that no one would easily recognize me.
I was a thief there too, you see.
-What is that?
-Money.
It would seem peculiar
if no one took his money after he died.
You can keep it.
I did not want to harm anyone
from Sari Village.
Mu-deok is in the capital.
If I ever run into her,
will I have to kill her too?
Is Broker Kim from Sari Village here?
Yes, he just arrived.
He is in the last room
on the second floor.
Young Lady Jin?
What brings you to a place like this?
It is none of your business.
You did not see me here.
Young Lady Jin, by any chance…
Do you gamble?
What? Gamble?
What do you take me for?
Do I seem that vulgar to you?
No, of course not.
But you lied and told me
the jade was not broken when it was.
Given you are capable of lying
without feeling the least bit of guilt,
I thought you would have
a knack for gambling.
I came to buy tickets from a scalper.
The tickets to a magic show were sold out.
That is why I am here.
ADMISSION TICKET
SEOCHUN MAGICIANS
-You got two tickets.
-I am going with my mother.
Do not tell anyone you saw me here.
I do not wish to cause
any misunderstandings.
I cannot guarantee that.
I am not as good of a liar
as you are, you see.
So if someone asks,
I am not sure if I can lie.
But I will try my best for your sake.
Why did I have to run into her here?
What is the leader of Songrim doing here?
I hope he is not here
to get tickets to the magic show.
If he goes, I will not be able to go
with Young Master Park.
You must be the one
who killed him.
It was not me.
Why did you kill him?
It really was not me.
He was already dead when I came here.
He was killed not too long ago.
It was done in a single stroke.
Whoever did this is a skilled swordsman.
I swear it was not me.
I do not even have a sword.
I think they were killed
by the same person.
Who are these men?
They were a group of thugs
who recently entered the capital.
Did they come with Broker Kim
who came from Sari Village?
No.
But I remember these thugs
picking a fight with him a few days ago.
They wanted to know the whereabouts
of a female swindler from Sari Village.
A swindler from Sari Village?
Could that be Mu-deok?
Where is she?
She was right behind me.
She ran away.
What is going on?
What were all those bodies?
They wanted to know the whereabouts
of a female swindler from Sari Village.
Could that really be me?
What kind of life has Mu-deok led?
Did you meet with So-i?
I wonder what she did this time.
Do not get involved with her.
So-i…
Who is So-i?
I did not see the girl
who came to see you.
But she quarreled with the guards
and even slapped one of them.
So I am sure the guards
would remember her face.
Madam, neither of those guards
came to work today.
-They both did not come?
-No.
How strange. They never miss work.
We are sorry.
How we acted was no way to treat a mage.
But is this really necessary?
"Mage"?
You even lied that you were a mage?
I will soon become one.
One who is far more prestigious
than the likes of you.
How dare you talk down to me
when you are nothing but a fake?
I will continue to talk down to you
while you speak to me with respect.
That is how things will be.
Go after him.
That is your job.
Is there a girl named Mu-deok
from Sari Village at Chwiseonru?
Yes, I know her. Was she the person
you were looking for that night?
I had to ask her for a favor
and return something to her.
Mu-deok is not at Chwiseonru.
She works as a maid for the Jang family,
the family of Cheonbugwan's Gwanju.
She is working as a maid?
I guess she really can see now.
She must have fooled you too.
We brought her to Chwiseonru
thinking she was blind,
but we were shocked
when she opened her eyes and ran.
But she is not a swindler like I am.
How is she able to see?
Please do not kill me.
I am sorry.
You know my face,
so I cannot let you live.
Please…
If she was always able to see,
that means she might recognize me.
She works as a maid for the Jang family?
I should pay her a visit.
Mu-deok committed murder?
Several men died at the ferry inn,
and Mu-deok was there.
But Mu-deok is not strong enough
to kill someone.
Especially not enough to kill several men.
It was done by a skilled swordsman.
If it was not her,
she likely received help from a mage.
Do not tell me
that you are suspecting Young Master Jang.
I am not.
Uk is currently at the palace
with Master Lee.
Thank goodness.
It could not have been Mu-deok.
She has no reason to harm anyone.
Maidservant Kim.
How much do you know about Mu-deok?
Do you know
what kind of life she led
before she started working here?
What?
The man who died
was someone I had met
to ask about Mu-deok's past.
A group of thugs
who seemed to be looking for her
was also killed.
It was obvious that
she was bound to get suspected,
but she ran away
instead of proving her innocence.
One thing is for sure.
Mu-deok is hiding something
that must not be revealed.
The guards live over there.
But would it not be faster
to just draw a sketch of her
and find her yourself?
I do not know what she looks like.
-I met her when I was blind.
-I thought you were never blind.
One day, you say you were blind.
The next day, you say you were not.
I do not know your reasons
but you live such a complicated life.
So you do not know what she looks like,
but she knows you?
Then would it not be dangerous
to look for her?
What if she killed the broker
and those thugs?
She might try to harm you too.
It is more dangerous to be suspected
by the leader of Songrim.
It will put you in trouble too
since you paid the broker.
What do you mean?
I do not know what you are talking about.
Good.
Just keep acting like
you do not know anything.
Someone is dead!
Guard Lee and Guard Jang are both dead.
What Hwansu entails is truly impressive.
I thought all soul shifters were monsters.
But in your case,
you gained youth and eternal life.
It is no wonder that
everyone wanted the ice stone
for the alchemy of souls.
Everyone coveted it,
which led to endless fights.
And that is why it was banned.
All right, Master Lee.
You say you can recognize soul shifters.
Take a look around.
Are there any soul shifters
in this palace?
I cannot tell just by looking at them.
If they do not show their blue marks
or run wild and get petrified,
they look no different
from ordinary humans.
Then how do you recognize them?
The fear of getting caught.
The horror of getting petrified.
I must bring that out of them.
So you recognize them by instilling fear?
I apologize if I disappointed you.
Instead,
I will give you a gift, Your Majesty.
A gift? What have you brought?
A dog.
A dog?
He is a very clever and gentle dog.
He should be in front
of the royal palace by now.
May I bring him inside?
You brought him as a gift, so of course.
Bring him in.
Uk.
I want you to go and bring the dog.
If you successfully bring him in,
I shall give you a reward.
Should I just leave
and run away with Mu-deok?
If I do that, everyone will find out.
And right now, I am not strong enough
to protect my master.
I wonder what Master Lee plans to do.
Assistant Gwanju, sir.
What is it?
Fluffy is the gift that
Master Lee brought for His Majesty?
Master Lee told me that
the dog will follow you inside.
But still, be careful.
Is it that dangerous
to take this dog into the palace?
What is the big deal?
It is Gwigu.
He is bringing Gwigu into the palace.
But Gwigu is a wily beast.
How could he bring
a wily beast into the palace?
Master Seo Gyeong,
who was my master long ago,
used Gwigu to find evil relics
that were created with sorcery
using the power of the ice stone.
Yes, I have heard of it.
However, I was told that it became useless
after Gwigu's pottery broke.
That is why
I moved the spirit of Gwigu
from the pottery into a dead dog.
The dog that will soon arrive
is Gwigu.
Gwigu?
What should we do?
How many of us are in the palace?
There are more than ten.
Did you report this to Cheonbugwan?
I sent someone there,
so they will be here soon.
We arranged today's meeting to make peace
between Songrim and the royal family.
The Crown Prince was kind enough
to visit you and invite you over himself.
But you wish to bring this wily beast
into the place
without His Majesty's permission?
He gave me permission to bring in the dog.
And right now, Gwigu cannot go wild
and cause danger
since it lives inside the body of a dog.
So it cannot harm a soul shifter
even if it sees one?
Instead, it will let you know by barking.
Bark.
Bark!
Oh, my goodness!
It is a soul shifter.
As expected, there are
more soul shifters within the palace.
What was that sound?
Does this mean there is a soul shifter
inside my palace?
It seems so.
Then why are you just standing there?
Get out there and catch the soul shifter.
Like I told you earlier,
I brought the dog as a gift.
I will leave it here with you.
You can use it to find
or catch the soul shifters
inside the palace, Your Majesty.
Take it away. We do not need it.
How dare you bring a wily beast
inside the palace!
His Majesty already suffers from anxiety.
Are you trying to harm him
with that wily beast of yours?
Mother, we were the ones
who invited Master Lee to the palace.
Stay out of this.
The mages of Cheonbugwan
are in charge of protecting the palace.
If there is anything made with sorcery
inside the palace,
they will be the ones to get rid of it.
I do not wish for a wily beast
living inside a dead dog
and the people of Songrim to interfere.
It is merely an attempt to humiliate us.
You must stop them, Your Majesty.
The son of Cheonbugwan's Gwanju
should be protecting the royal family,
but you brought in a wily beast instead.
It is Master Lee's gift for the King.
Please let us in.
I was told to safely bring him inside.
Is that so?
Then try your best to get inside.
Kill the wily beast
that has trespassed the palace.
If you successfully bring him in,
I shall give you a reward.
Damn it.
Is this why he picked me to do this?
Your Majesty, it is I, Jin Mu.
I shall get rid of
these insolent men from Songrim.
His Majesty has invited us here
and we are still talking.
Jin Mu, this is not
your place to interfere.
How dare you bring in that dog
without permission!
What kind of crazy act is this?
Silence.
Guards! What are you doing? Stop that man!
Father.
You must stop both of them.
If this leads to a fight,
it will end our relationship with Songrim.
We must fight.
Songrim has brought
a wily beast into the royal palace.
It is Cheonbugwan's job to protect us.
-Father!
-Your Majesty!
I order all of you…
to stop.
Stop!
Master Lee.
I invited you over for a friendly meeting.
Did you have to shock me like this?
I am sorry if I startled you.
Your Majesty, if the ice stone
gets revealed to the world,
a greater conflict will arise.
The ice stone?
Is it because of the soul shifters?
People have occasionally used
the remaining Soul Ejectors
to shift souls after the Great Chaos.
Someone seems to be
making Soul Ejectors again.
The ice stone has come out into the world.
So what are you saying?
Where is it? In whose hands?
Probably in the hands of those
who sent Naksu here and turned
a Songrim mage into a soul shifter.
I was told that Master Seo Gyeong
destroyed all the ice stones 200 years ago
after the Great Chaos.
However,
I guess not all were destroyed
and instead left in Songrim.
It is not easy to quell human desires.
However,
the return of the ice stone
also implies the return
of a great man like Master Seo Gyeong.
Master Seo Gyeong was born
with the energy of the King's Star.
However, he did not become the king.
Are you saying there could be
another person born with the energy
of the King's Star?
Even if he exists,
the light he emits will be faint.
And the energy of the seven stars
surrounding him will not show yet.
A power strong enough
to defy the laws of nature
and bring chaos to the world
has returned once again.
Thus, someone strong enough
to stop it should also appear.
That way,
the world will be able
to maintain balance.
What I am trying to say is that
there is no need to feel so anxious.
I hope this helps you calm your anxiety.
Thank you for your words of comfort.
Then I should leave now.
As you refused to accept my gift,
I will take Gwigu back with me.
-Your Majesty.
-Do as you please.
No, wait. Stop.
Are we leaving?
I saw everything that I needed to see.
Does this mean there is a soul shifter
inside my palace?
Take it away. We do not need it.
How dare you bring a wily beast
inside the palace!
They revealed themselves
after I instilled fear.
You must have been startled.
Are you all right?
How did you get hurt?
The dog did not get hurt.
But thanks to you, I did.
Did you get hurt?
I cannot believe you got hurt
fighting those goons.
He still has a long way to go, right?
Wait. I see blood. Are you hurt?
That is my blood.
He did not get hurt at all…
-Wait, blood…
-You are bleeding.
Thank goodness.
Does it hurt?
I guess it does.
It hurts. My gosh.
That Gwigu belongs to Master Lee.
How much does he know about Mu-deok?
And what will Uk do
if he finds out about Naksu?
Are you all right?
You are hurt all over.
I am fine.
Did you find the soul shifters?
What about the ice stone?
You have no idea.
My soul almost shifted
because of the chaos.
So you caused a scene
but failed to find anyone?
You should have at least
let the dog bite someone.
Uk.
Finding a soul shifter in the royal palace
is different from finding one
in Songrim or Cheonbugwan.
If things get out of hand,
it will turn into a fight
between Songrim and the royal family.
Let us go.
You should get treated.
Master Lee.
Please wait here for a bit.
The Crown Prince has asked me
to escort you to his palace.
-The Crown Prince?
-It will rain soon.
He wants you to stay until the rain stops.
Let us go then.
Uk, you need to take him back first.
Take him to Songrim.
Come here.
Come on.
You should have told me
before the people of Songrim arrived!
I thought it was just
going to be a simple meeting.
If the Queen is put in danger,
you will also get petrified
just like Eunuch Kim.
You useless imbecile!
Someone born with the energy
of the King's Star
who will follow the footsteps
of Master Seo Gyeong?
If it is revealed that King's Star
was created by sorcery,
it will spell the end of Songrim.
I sent back Gwigu to Songrim.
I apologize for startling you.
After a soul shifter was found in Songrim,
I figured there could be one
in the palace as well.
Last time, a soul shifter even tried
to enter the royal palace.
I heard the person who created
and killed the soul shifter was Naksu.
Naksu?
The female assassin
who killed many skilled fighters.
Heads fell to the ground
wherever she went,
which is why she was called Naksu.
There are rumors that
she shifted souls and is still alive.
Naksu, a soul shifter?
What an interesting rumor.
I hope Mu-deok gets caught
before Young Master Jang returns.
Oh, my goodness!
Mu-deok…
Why are you shaking?
Do you really believe
that I killed someone?
Come inside.
Why did you come here?
To pack your things and run?
I came to ask you for a favor.
The leader of Songrim asked me
to bring you in if I ever saw you.
Mu-deok.
It was not you, was it?
-It was not me.
-Then why did you run away?
The situation made me do so.
Mu-deok.
Do you have
some big secret you are hiding?
Does Young Master Jang
also know about your secret?
Mu-deok, I want you to run away.
I will give you enough money.
Run away and never come back.
I cannot do that.
I cannot leave Young Master Jang.
Why not?
Young Master Jang will only fall
under suspicion if you stay by his side.
If you are worried about him,
you must help me.
You refuse to talk to Songrim's leader
or run away.
What do you plan to do?
I must find the real assassin.
That assassin is going around
killing everyone that knows them.
Is this where Cheonbugwan's Gwanju lives?
It must be a very prestigious family.
Does someone from the Jang family
also know you?
Wait over there by the corner.
I will bring that person to you.
I am going to ask someone to testify
that I was not in the room
when those people were killed at the inn.
Who are you going to ask?
Young Lady Jin from Jinyowon.
I ran into her at the inn.
That catty young lady will not
agree to see you.
Maidservant Kim.
I want you to take me to Jinyowon.
Jinyowon?
I am sorry.
Could you pick up the cane for me?
Thank you.
Can you tell me where I am right now?
This is the house of Master Jang,
the Gwanju of Cheonbugwan.
I see.
Thank you.
Mu-deok.
Let us go.
I guess Mu-deok really can see now.
But she did not recognize me.
I wonder if that is a good thing.
Why are you alone?
I was mistaken.
It turns out I did not know her at all.
It is all over now.
Let us return to Cheonbugwan.
Can I try it?
-No.
Come on. Stop it.
I am getting all wet.
It is that umbrella.
This is an umbrella.
You can use this as a cane.
Stop it. My mom will scold me.
Stop it already!
-No way.
-Hey, kid.
Would you like
to switch umbrellas with me?
I heard Naksu shifted her soul
into the body of
a tall, well-built young man.
She could have shifted her soul
into the body of a short, petite woman.
If she entered such a weak body,
there would be no need to discard her.
No, I am telling you.
Naksu in Blue was clearly a man.
"Naksu in Blue."
-I have also heard of that nickname.
-He covered himself with a blue cloth.
It became such a trend
that everyone was wearing blue cloth.
People wore blue cloths
because they thought
Naksu in Blue would protect them
from the alchemy of souls.
Naksu may have been an assassin,
but she never hurt ordinary people
and was very strong.
People can be very foolish.
They are not foolish.
They are frightened.
Naksu's body was burned,
and they all know that
it was done by those
with power and authority.
Calling them fools
when they are actually scared
is negligence.
I gathered this meeting
hoping to think of a solution,
but you are arrogant enough
to just sit there and criticize me.
I understand that
you two wish to disparage each other,
but I wish for all of us
to get along amicably.
Master Lee is also here with us.
Let us drink our tea.
Your Royal Highness.
What is it?
Young Lady Heo wishes to come inside.
Let her in.
What brings you here?
I heard someone was injured
after getting into a fight.
I came to take a look.
There is only one person who got hurt.
-Take him out and treat his wound.
-I am all right.
It will not take long.
Please come with me.
It seems like Uk will get engaged again.
How many times is this?
-What do you mean?
-Did you not know?
You really know nothing, do you?
Rumor has already spread in Sejukwon.
You three are the top potential candidates
to become Heo Yeom's grandson-in-law.
Uk is the third on his list.
But I guess to her, he is the first.
Heo Yeom wishes to marry her off
within this year.
There will soon be talks of engagement.
I promise you.
The cut is not too deep.
This pill can help stop the bleeding.
Then you could have just
given it to me earlier.
I heard you were hurt.
I wanted to see for myself
so I could feel at ease.
Well…
You already got hurt from the many duels,
so I was concerned.
I am fine.
All right.
Oh, right. Maidservant Kim
gave this to me as a gift.
I have not yet been able to thank you.
It looks exactly the same.
What do you mean?
It is exactly the same
as the one I have seen for 20 years.
Is it a valuable item?
It looks new.
So it probably is not ours.
They made it look so similar.
Goodness.
The Crown Prince might be right.
Uk really might get engaged soon.
But to Master Heo,
he is the third in line.
Then do you plan to marry her
since you are the first in line?
If you get married,
you will have to return to Seoho Fortress.
Yul, do not get married.
I will feel lonely without you.
I can recognize soul shifters.
I must take them to Seoho Fortress
as soon as possible.
Who?
Me?
I take that back.
I feel very much at ease
after having seen how you reacted today.
I am relieved to hear that.
What is that you wish
to ask me for in private?
I know you took Naksu's sword,
but would it be possible
to give that to me?
I did watch the magic show last year.
I even saw elephants.
But I should act like it is my first time
when I go with Young Master Park, right?
So you got those tickets
for you and Young Master Park.
You startled me. What are you doing here?
I came to ask you for a favor.
A favor?
Do not bother.
I have no intentions of helping you.
I am being framed for murder.
What?
Can you please tell the leader of Songrim
that you saw me earlier at the inn?
You want me to go to Songrim
and tell him that I had set foot
at a place like that?
I would be mad to do that.
You are my only hope.
I beg of you to help.
No.
I told Young Master Park
that I had an extra ticket.
I do not want to reveal
I bought them from a scalper.
Your embarrassment will only be temporary,
but I could really get killed for this.
If my mother finds out, she will kill me.
There is no way
she would kill her own daughter!
Why are you yelling?
You came to ask for a favor.
Then I guess I have no choice
but to tell your mother what happened
and ask her to help me instead.
You are going to ask my mother?
There she is.
You did not need to bring gifts
to apologize for the past.
The more I thought about it,
the more apologetic I felt.
I will go and ask her myself.
Wait.
I will think about it. Come with me first.
I will be right back. Stay here.
If you do not come, I will yell.
-I will be back.
-Cho-yeon.
Yes, Mother.
Wait here.
She is a young girl.
I wonder who she is.
Is it because of the incense stick?
What a nice vase.
If you put flowers in the vase,
it helps them emit a stronger scent.
-Really?
-Yes.
I have been wanting to change
the vase in my daughter's room.
Thank you.
Mother, are you going to put the vase
in Bu-yeon's room?
It helps the flowers emit
a stronger scent.
Your sister cannot see, so she should
at least enjoy the scent of the flowers.
How dare you touch that!
What are you doing in my daughter's room?
She came with me.
She must have gotten lost.
Mu-deok, what were you doing here?
I am sorry.
Please help me, just this once.
Please leave.
You are not allowed in here.
All right. Let us leave.
I promise I will go.
Cho-yeon.
Tell the servants
to clean Bu-yeon's room again.
Yes, Mother.
So-i.
This man will be your father.
My father?
A father is willing to take in
a fake daughter?
I am not the father of Jin Bu-yeon.
Jin Bu-yeon's biological father
is someone else.
To be acknowledged
as the daughter of the Jin family,
you must open the door to Jinyowon.
And to do that, the blood
of the Jin family needs to run inside you.
What is that?
A worm that sucked the blood
of a female member of the Jin family.
That is the blood of Cho-yeon,
my beloved daughter.
What do you plan to do with that?
Give me your hand.
I said, give me your hand.
You now have the blood of the Jin family
running inside you.
If I do not use sorcery to keep it alive,
that worm will start eating you
from the inside.
If you try to run from me,
that worm will eat you alive.
That room belonged to her daughter
who died ten years ago.
She apparently drowned and died,
but Lady Jin still thinks
she might come back.
She is a pitiful woman,
so forgive her for slapping you.
By any chance, was that daughter blind?
Yes, she was.
The owner of this body
used to be blind as well.
Could that be why
I suddenly felt something earlier?
Master Lee wanted to talk
to the Crown Prince in private.
I see.
The leader has asked us
to escort you to Songrim.
Just me? Why?
Come with us.
Am I getting locked in here again?
-What is going on?
-It is--
We were told to stay silent.
Wait here until he comes.
Mu-deok was found near the bodies,
so I get why she was taken away.
But why Young Master Jang?
He was at the palace.
What is the leader of Songrim thinking?
I do not know either.
Yul.
Mu-deok would never kill anyone.
Right?
May I take a look at the bodies?
It was done by a skilled swordsman.
It could not have been Mu-deok.
But she is the assassin, Naksu.
She could have killed those men.
I have a good reason for doing this,
so just go on your way.
-They are those thugs.
-Do you know them?
I got into a fight with them
some time ago.
Can I take their bodies now
and hold a funeral for them?
What brings the owner of Chwiseonru here?
Did someone die?
Our guards got killed.
Young Master Park.
Maidservant Kim told me what happened.
Young Lady Jin.
Please help Mu-deok.
I went to the inn
to buy tickets from scalpers.
And I saw Mu-deok there.
But of course,
it was my first time
going to such a place.
I know.
We talked for a bit,
and right after Mu-deok went inside,
I saw you coming in, my lord.
And of course,
I never thought I would meet you there.
I know.
Judging by the circumstances,
there is no way Mu-deok had enough time
to kill all those men.
A girl recently came
to Chwiseonru and looked for Mu-deok,
pretending to be a mage.
The owner of Chwiseonru thinks
it might have been So-i,
the girl that the broker warned her about.
I once saw a girl
arguing with those thugs.
The dead broker,
thugs, and guards.
They all had something to do
with that girl, So-i.
That swindler, So-i, seems suspicious.
In any case, it means Mu-deok is innocent.
All right.
I also did not think that
Mu-deok would have committed murder.
I knew it. You knew that Mu-deok would
never do such a thing, right?
Then can you release Uk and Mu-deok now?
The reason I locked both of them up
was to ask them about something else.
I will take care of it from here.
You may all leave.
All right.
My lord.
What is this?
At least tell me what is going on.
Mu-deok committed murder.
What--
She killed those who knew about her past.
Tell me what it is that you and Mu-deok
are hiding from me.
If your statement
does not match Mu-deok's,
you will not be able
to leave this Secret Room.
And Mu-deok will die.
My lord, hear me out--
This is not about the murders.
Uk has told me your secret.
He told me everything.
If you also tell me the truth,
I shall spare your life.
However,
if anything that you say
differs from what he said,
you will die.
If he found out she was a soul shifter,
he would not waste time like this.
He is trying to test us
by interrogating us separately.
We have to say the same thing.
What would Uk have said
to the same question?
A secret that ensures
that we say the same thing.
A secret that is private
but will not get me killed if revealed.
I will tell you the truth.
I will tell you my secret.
What happened?
Both Mu-deok and Uk
can be set free.
What did they say?
Did they say the same thing?
They both did say the same thing.
-You got out.
-So did you.
-I am relieved that you are all right.
-Yes, me too.
Thank goodness we said the same thing.
What did you say?
The fact that we both got out…
means you said
the same thing as what I said.
You separately locked them up
to find out what they were hiding.
I guess you got something out of them.
Tell me.
What was the secret they were hiding?
The two of them…
told me a secret
that completely shut me up.
They both showed me the same thing.
I will tell you the truth.
I tried not to let it show.
This is what I kept inside.
You see, I…
I actually…
I like Mu-deok a lot.
I like Young Master Jang very much.
I figured it would ensure
that we said the same thing.
It was not crucial enough
to get me killed.
Right. Songrim's Book of Regulations
does not state anything about
punishing young men and women
for falling in love.
Exactly.
They would not kill a maid
for loving her owner to death.
You said that?
You told him that you loved me to death?
Well…
I just exaggerated
because I had to convince him.
I had no choice but to say it.
You had no choice but to admit
that you loved me to death.
Gosh, I feel so bad.
I was not as passionate
when I expressed my feelings.
I guess I should try harder.
Forget it.
Do not put everything on the line
for something as fickle as love.
If something like this ever happens again,
and you find yourself
in a life or death situation,
give up on love…
and choose your life.
Do that if you do not wish to die.
That is an order from your master.
Master.
What if I do not mind dying?
Then can I hold onto it
and keep loving you?
I told you that
I am willing to risk it all
and that we are in this together.
I will keep going no matter what.
So you should do the same
and stick to your confession.
Keep loving me to death.
If Uk falls in love
with a woman he should not,
what would you do?
If I am to stay in love with you,
I need to be certain you are mine.
How dare you disgrace Jinyowon?
-This is too salty!
-They are perfect for each other.
Why call off the wedding?
I am looking for Shaman Choi.
If Shaman Choi was hunted by
the mages of Cheonbugwan,
are you seeking her because
she bears a grudge against your father?
If he comes, let me know immediately.
Even though it is dead, it is still Gwigu.
You are feigning ignorance, right?
It must be tough for you.
If you must draw
and point that sword at someone,
point it at me before at anyone else.
Subtitle translation by: Ja-won Lee