Thank you for the tour.
- Please let me know if you are interested.
- Sure.
This place is
right between Jinyowon and Songrim.
The roof tiles and the floors are clean.
This is the best house we have seen.
Do you not think there are too many rooms?
They will have children soon.
A son will take the surname Park
and lead Songrim,
and a daughter will take the surname Jin
and lead Jinyowon.
They will need to bear many children.
I am glad I asked you to come
on this house tour with me.
I will decide on the house you prefer.
Sure.
To be honest,
I do not wish to live in a big house.
I would much rather prefer a cozy house
where my husband and I
can live happily together.
It would be nice to have a small garden
where I can plant my favorite flowers.
You do like flowers, do you not?
How about planting some balsam?
My husband and I could dye
each other's fingernails with its flowers.
It would be wonderful
to live such a happy life together.
I will look for a house
that befits your description.
Pardon?
I will get a house with a small garden
and plant balsam seeds.
I will gift it to you
on your wedding day.
Gift it to me?
Since Master Lee adored Sapsali,
I will also gift you a puppy.
Are you telling me to wed Master Lee?
You said just looking at him
made you happy.
Did you think
Master Lee was the one I had feelings for?
I am not that dense, you know?
So that is why you so thoughtfully offered
to give me a house
as a wedding gift if I marry him?
I can give you that much.
Better yet,
you should get me a house
with 100 rooms. You are well-off.
A hundred rooms?
Did you actually prefer a big house?
You see, I am a bit slow.
Are you a fool?
You are the one I have feelings for.
I was hoping
you would catch on to it sooner or later.
While cooking your favorite dishes
and making your clothes,
even though you are slow, I thought you
would one day catch on to my feelings.
That was my hope.
But you want me to wed
some other man instead?
You will buy me a house
when I wed someone else?
Maidservant Kim.
I must have misunderstood you.
Shut up!
While house touring together,
I dreamed of the day
when we would wed as well.
I imagined us lovingly dyeing
each other's fingernails
with the balsam flowers
that we picked from our garden.
Lovingly?
Yes! Lovingly!
Being lovey-dovey!
Lovingly!
Right! Lovingly!
That image looks so vivid to me as well.
Forget it.
You have broken my dream.
I will no longer expect anything from you.
Right. I will accept a house
with 100 rooms on my wedding day.
I…
Maidservant Kim!
Maidservant Kim.
Lovingly.
I have ruined everything.
You fool.
Fine.
I will wed someone like you told me to.
You had better get me
that house with 100 rooms.
You were here.
Maidservant Kim, are you crying?
Of course not. Why would I?
You are crying. Who made you cry?
Seeing you cry breaks my heart.
I am just jealous
that Young Master Park
is getting married before you do.
I am just jealous and upset.
There is no need to feel that way.
I will get married soon too.
What?
Have you finally decided to marry someone?
Yes, so there is nothing to be sad about.
Then…
Then I should just keep these here.
What is all this?
They are wedding gifts
I had been keeping for your wedding.
But I was going to give them
to the newlyweds.
Why give them all of this? What a waste.
Right?
I should give them
to Young Lady Heo, right?
Why would you do that?
You said you are getting married.
I already know.
She is your bird egg.
- Bird egg?
- Your secret love.
A sophisticated egret
that will hatch in a tall tree.
You have it all wrong.
That is the wrong bird.
- Is it not her?
- No.
I thought she must be
the one who would hatch.
Then is there someone else?
Yes, there is.
Who is it?
Maidservant Kim, do not be startled.
If you are too shocked,
just bite down on your handkerchief.
But who could it be?
There has been no woman around you.
It cannot possibly be…
That is right.
This will all be for Mu-deok.
That cannot be.
That cannot be!
What happened to Young Lady Heo?
I guess things worked out
for you and Young Master Jang.
Yes.
I have decided to get married to him.
You know I am fond of spreading rumors.
Please do so. Let everyone know
that I have changed my fate.
Word of your marriage will clear up
all of his unsavory rumors.
"Unsavory rumors"?
Rumor had it that he was impotent
since he practiced chastity.
That is not true!
That was what everyone said.
Is it not true?
That is definitely not the case. Jeez.
You have confirmed it for yourself.
What do you mean?
I get it now.
That is why you have chosen to wed him.
What woman would marry an impotent man
even if he was from the Jang family?
Do not worry.
You can rest assured
that I will tell others.
"She checked, and he is not impotent."
We have not slept together yet.
We seriously have not!
Do not be embarrassed.
I am older than you.
You were just full of malice
when we first met.
But you seem to have a heart now.
I always thought that you could cut ties
with everyone and disappear.
I told you. I changed my fate.
I will stay here
and protect those whom I love.
You must like him a lot.
I hope you have a happy married life.
I will find the sword
that can help you destroy Jang Uk.
I am the only one who can protect you
by getting rid of the King's Star.
Jang Uk has lost all his energy.
He gave it all up to break the barrier.
He is no longer eligible
to be the next Gwanju.
He has lost all power.
And everyone already thinks
the King's Star has risen for me.
There is nothing more
that you can do for me, Assistant Gwanju.
Jang Gang sacrificed himself to keep
Songrim, Jinyowon, and Cheonbugwan safe.
But since Jin U-tak is alive,
you will be found guilty.
I do not want to punish my former master.
Come clean and accept your punishment.
Do you truly think the ice stone is gone?
That stone gets its power from the sky.
The one who was born
with the energy of the King's Star
is awarded that power.
What would you do
if he was actually hiding his power?
I will wait for your reply.
My loyalty will forever lie with you,
Your Royal Highness.
Why have you not said anything
after regaining consciousness?
I have only saved you
so you may atone for your sins
in front of our daughter,
Bu-yeon.
When we first met,
I fell for your warm smile.
This looks pretty too.
I think Bu-yeon
will look good in this too.
Ever since the moment
I had fallen for you,
I have
never loved
anyone else.
I am not trying to clear up
any misunderstanding.
I am saying this so you will suffer.
I want you to know
exactly what you did to our daughter
after being deceived by Jin Mu.
And I hope you will be in agony.
Jin U-tak is in Sejukwon.
He has regained consciousness.
If he is alive,
he will definitely expose me
and our organization.
We must get rid of him.
I have brought the Queen's soul potions
and the divination bells as you commanded.
I can make all the soul shifters
I have created go on a rampage with this.
If Jang Uk really has
the ice stone's power,
he will have no choice but to reveal it.
Please craft two rings with these.
Seeing how
you are ordering matching rings,
I guess the rumors are true.
They are wedding rings,
so please make them well.
Of course.
I will do my utmost best.
Please take a look at these designs.
Which one do you like?
I like this one.
No!
That one is…
That was Young Lady Yeong-ok's ring.
- Not that one.
- All right.
It is not pretty.
- Then what about this one?
- No...
Well…
- Young Lady So-jeong…
- Never mind.
All of these are not my style.
I will take out the ones
that do not suit your taste.
These…
And these too…
All right.
Feel free to choose
from the remaining ones.
Seven rings?
Wait.
I do not think there were seven.
I really do not remember any of them.
Were all of them like Cho-yeon?
Did you promise to wed them
if they opened your gate of energy?
I swear. I never seduced them first.
You once said that you needed to make
an effort not to like a handsome man.
They all lacked in that aspect.
How annoying.
In any case, I am now all yours.
Are you not proud
that you beat
all the others to win my heart?
I would have been prouder
had there been a dozen.
What a shame, right?
Do you think there were not a dozen?
I am just kidding. You are the only one.
I have forgotten them all.
Hold on.
I did see a few rings
while cleaning your room.
I must look for them.
Why would you look
for those meaningless rings?
No, I am pretty sure
there were around a dozen of them.
Let go. I need to check.
There are none.
Mu-deok, shall we go eat?
Be honest.
How many rings?
Just one.
I will hold your hand as if it is a ring.
This is a one-of-a-kind ring.
Well…
Since we already have rings,
we will not need to make any
with the yin-and-yang jade.
Should we make necklaces
with this instead?
Do as you please.
I am not jealous of Dang-gu one bit.
- I am not jealous of Cho-yeon either.
- I guess the rumors are true.
That impertinent young master is smiling.
You are right.
I guess I had misunderstood
everything from the beginning.
How embarrassing.
Young Lady Heo.
Do not tell me you confessed your love
to him when you were trapped together.
I was going to. And I almost did.
I had my chance.
You do not need to hold that up for me.
You can place it down.
Are you uncomfortable that I am here?
I am fine.
You can do as you please.
When you were drunk
and lying down in Sejukwon,
you were comfortable with me
taking care of you all night.
Because I thought you were Mu-deok.
So that is how he looks
when he is around someone he likes.
If Young Master Jang got hurt
instead of Young Master Seo,
you two would have gotten closer.
Because you treat those who are hurt.
Do you think so?
Had he gotten injured,
would I have had a chance?
Yul, I heard you were returning
to Seoho Fortress.
Yes, after attending Dang-gu's wedding.
Let us have a farewell party before then.
Sure.
Despite that your wound has healed,
you are still experiencing pain?
I thought it would get better,
but I was wrong.
Did something else happen
while I was unconscious
in the barrier?
We just stopped the bleeding
from your wound.
So-i, who ran away, gave you her blood.
You cannot give blood this way.
Why were you so reckless?
I just wanted
to save him.
Her blood did enter your wound.
But that should not be a problem.
I am sure I will recover soon.
I do not want the elders to worry,
so please keep it a secret.
All right. Drink up.
Hey, what are you doing there?
What did you steal from...
What is this?
Hey! Stop there!
The wound where the worm left
is not healing quickly.
There is a blood parasite in his body.
He must be in pain.
He should take the medicine I took
in Jinyowon to relieve the pain.
Mu-deok.
You should stop working here.
What is it? Are you kicking me out?
If I was, would you listen?
- No.
- I knew you would not.
Do not turn me into a bad person.
Do not do household chores anymore.
You will be his precious wife,
so I cannot make you work.
Does that mean you will accept me?
What choice do I have?
He absolutely adores you.
Also, I will not address you as "my lady."
Goodness.
I will not consider you
my mother-in-law either.
Why would I be your mother-in-law
when I am still single?
That would hurt my pride.
That is true.
But you and the leader
will get married soon, right?
I thought you liked each other.
Unbelievable.
Maidservant Kim.
Even you can tell that, but he cannot.
- Gosh.
- Hold on.
How could he possibly be that slow?
Is he a fool?
He sure is.
Goodness.
Yes! Lovingly! Being lovey-dovey!
I just cannot
forget those words
that she has said
to me.
My lord.
Uk.
When did you get here?
I was here for a while.
I had something to tell you.
What are you thinking about so intensely?
Something terrible
has been bothering me.
What do you need to tell me?
You see…
I am planning to leave the capital
for some time after Dang-gu's wedding.
I see.
Then…
What about Maidservant Kim?
Goodness.
If no one wants her to stay here,
then I will have to bring her with me.
We do not know when we will return.
It could be one year or ten years.
Or we may just never return.
I have done something
unforgivable to her.
Oh, dear.
If I hold on to her,
do you think she will stay?
She…
shed some tears.
She will cry even harder
if you do not stop her from leaving.
I will leave
with Young Master Jang.
I will not.
I will.
There is no point in staying. I should go.
There is something I would like
to show you.
They are balsam seeds.
If you plant these right now,
the flowers will bloom
in three to four months.
I could make them bloom
in front of your eyes right now
by using a spell.
But…
I tend to be slow.
I would like to wait
and watch them sprout, grow,
and bloom.
Can you wait with me?
Of course.
I will walk
at your pace.
This gift will only interrupt them.
Thank you. We will enjoy the fish.
Thank you.
Did you see that?
That man was crying.
I have never seen an adult cry
with a runny nose before.
He must be ill.
Do you think so?
Are you all right?
I have brought you some medicine.
Here.
Once Shaman Choi's brother
who is in Sejukwon starts talking,
we will be able to catch Jin Mu soon.
There is something I must ask Jin Mu.
Whether my father chose
to become a soul shifter
or if there was a story behind it.
Only he will know.
Lord Cho Chung passed away
because of Gwanju Jang Gang.
Lord Cho found out
that the Gwanju had practiced sorcery.
Afraid that Lord Cho would tell the truth,
Jin Mu turned him into a soul shifter
and made him run wild.
Are you saying
we killed him
when he was actually innocent?
It is not our fault.
We were not aware of that situation.
Everyone thinks
that Lord Cho killed his own family
after practicing sorcery.
The Gwanju implored
that Lord Cho's name is cleared.
We should discuss this
at the next Unanimous Assembly.
But why did Jin Mu go that far?
If he just wanted to silence Lord Cho,
why did he turn him
into a soul shifter
and make him kill his entire family?
Jin Mu knows everything
about the circumstances of Uk's birth.
He only did that
to Jang Gang's friend, Cho Chung,
solely to torture Jang Gang.
That means
if Jin Mu gets caught, he will expose
Young Master Jang's secret.
We cannot let that happen. Jin Mu…
must be killed.
If you cast a divination curse
on the Soul Ejector,
you can control the soul that uses it.
You can make him run wild
and then get rid of him by petrification.
Shaman Choi
cast divination curses
on all Soul Ejectors she had made.
That is why I have never
shifted souls to this day.
I will make all soul shifters
in this capital run wild
just like Cho Chung did that day.
Assistant Gwanju.
Jang Uk is going to leave Jeongjingak.
Songrim is letting him go?
That is what I heard.
Rumor has it
that he is leaving the capital as well.
He will leave everything behind?
Jang Uk is the only way I can hold on to
the Crown Prince. If he disappears…
There is nothing more
that you can do for me,
Assistant Gwanju.
Why in the world is he leaving Songrim?
He even consumed poison to get in there
and even reached Chisu.
He may even have the ice stone's power,
so why?
Maybe he had a change of heart.
That means he has changed.
Why do you think
he changed all of a sudden?
What made him change?
People change because of other people.
Find out who showed up
just when he began to change.
That will be your answer.
The person who showed up
just when he began to change…
I am here for Naksu's sword.
That is ridiculous.
It could not have been Naksu.
He used Tansu, which was Naksu's skill.
No.
He must have learned that from Master Lee.
I saw everything
during my time in Danhyanggok with him.
And by his side was
no one other than his maid.
Is he leaving with his maid?
Yes.
I heard he is leaving with Mu-deok,
the maid who always follows him around.
I feel bad about bringing you here.
You said you had a lot to buy.
I should help you carry them.
If she is who I think she is…
Mu-deok.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Did you not hear me calling you?
I did.
Why did I not answer?
Did you also hear bells?
Bells? No, I did not.
- This is not of good quality. Let us go.
- Sure.
Naksu.
You have given me hope.
Master Lee, there is one over there.
Gosh.
Come on.
Master Lee, you have been
letting them go countless times.
I do not have regrets
about the fish I have failed to catch.
What do you mean?
It would be a waste. It would be unfair.
That is being greedy and obsessive.
- What?
- However,
I saw there is pure sadness in loss.
Lately, I am starting
to understand why people feel sad
when they see a river running,
a season passing, and a sun setting.
Looking at this empty basket makes me sad.
Mu-deok told me to catch a lot of fish.
Do you plan to keep
the soul shifter by your side?
We kept our promise to you.
I stood in front of Naksu's sword,
and she put down her sword.
So I hope you will keep your end
of the bargain and let us go.
What happened to the ice stone that day?
Is it perhaps inside you?
Even if it is,
it is completely useless.
I can no longer catch a waterdrop,
let alone a Golden Fish.
If you train again,
you will be able to use that power.
I witnessed
how the desire to win that power
made people violent and evil.
It is only right
not to awaken the ice stone's power.
You are greedy with catching fish
but not with the ice stone?
You are better than me.
In any case, since I have the ice stone,
I can protect one individual.
If Mu-deok runs wild,
please help me use this power to stop it.
She will be fine as long as
she does not try to bring out her power.
That small, weak body is housing
the powerful soul of an assassin.
If anything, she would have
already run wild.
The reason why she has not
is that her body is
in control of the soul's power.
I could see that on the day we first met.
The only thing that can
encompass the powers of a mage
is the divine powers of priestesses.
I believe Mu-deok's body
originally belonged
to someone with great divine powers.
This will help relieve the pain.
It will only relieve the pain
but not get rid of it.
I need to give this to him.
So you have dug your own grave.
How dare you deceive me
by pretending to be my daughter,
So-i?
You were not fooled.
You knew but feigned ignorance.
Was it because of the ice stone?
That is right.
A mother can always recognize her child.
Before you run your mouth further,
it would be best
if I killed you here right now.
Can you also
recognize this?
Bu-yeon was wearing this
on the day she disappeared.
You said you embroidered it yourself.
Where did you get this?
Did Jin Mu give it to you?
No.
Only I know who its real owner is.
Tell me.
Your daughter is still alive.
Kill me,
and you will never see her again.
I will spare you.
Where is my daughter?
Do not rush me.
I will tell you
once I know that I am safe.
The ice stone has disappeared.
But there are still soul shifters
that the Choi siblings
and their gang have created.
Songrim and Jinyowon
will eliminate all of them.
I ask that you will help us as well.
You are implying that
I should not protect Jin Mu
even if he gets caught.
I know he was your master
but I believe you are not blinded by him.
So you trust me?
Then do you also believe
that I am the King's Star
who got rid of the ice stone?
The ice stone's barrier was lifted,
and you were there.
That was when the King's Star appeared.
So like everyone else,
I believe the King's Star was for you.
I was not the only one here that day.
Who would have minded them
when you were in their presence?
It was Jang Uk.
I am sure you saw him as well.
He is like a son to me.
You saved his life, Your Royal Highness.
I am truly grateful for that.
I will quit my job here in Songrim today.
I came to resign.
You really jumped through hoops
to land this job.
It is a shame that
you are quitting due to marriage.
Then again, you are trading it off
for becoming the lady of the Jang family.
Mu-deok, congratulations on your marriage.
Be happy.
Come on, now. Come.
Why are you standing there? Follow me.
Your Royal Highness,
thank you for saving my life.
I hope the King's Star will shine forever.
That is enough.
You do not need to pretend as well.
It is uncomfortable.
You already know that it was Jang Uk
who saved everyone that day.
Like you two have promised,
I will not tell a soul.
So do not worry.
Do I look worried that I will lose credit?
I am just annoyed by everyone's flattery.
They are all praising you.
You can just accept it for what it is.
It offends me to hear
such things from strangers.
Seeing you worship me
despite knowing everything…
feels like you are mocking me,
and I hate it.
I can empathize with you.
You will never see me again.
So do not worry.
I heard.
- You are leaving with him.
- Yes, Your Royal Highness.
We are going to go far away
from this capital and live together.
Together?
I could easily stop you from leaving.
Do you think I will let him go
when he knows my weakness?
Then how would it feel
to keep having him around you?
Then it would not
simply just offend you anymore.
Right.
You are Filthy Mu-deok
who listens to my petty complaints.
Then listen to this as well.
I will feel small, knowing that he did
something I had failed to do.
And pretending to have done something
I did not do will make me more pathetic.
But most of all,
I will vehemently despise…
seeing you two together.
I had told you before
that I do not hold on to things
that I know I cannot hold on to.
Do you know what happens
if I try and still fail to hold on?
Will you blame that individual
and get rid of them?
If this pathetic, wretched feeling
turns into a violent, wicked one,
simply avoiding me will not cut it.
Go far away…
where I cannot reach you.
Everyone.
I am getting married tomorrow!
You little boys.
We will not see each other
that often anymore.
Of course not.
Cho-yeon would not allow that.
- Neither will his mother-in-law.
- Right.
He will no longer come
to our polo matches.
Nor when we go fishing.
I can still make time
and see you every now and then.
What will you say?
Will you lie that you are training?
Are you seriously going to lie
to a Jinyowon priestess?
He will get caught right away.
She will surround you with her relics
and demand the truth.
Then you will be bewitched and come clean.
They will pluck all of his hair.
Oh, dear. He has thin hair to begin with.
I get it.
You are just envious of me.
I am still happy.
Because my first love came true.
I will give you bachelors my good energy.
- I caught it.
- Right, you have Mu-deok.
- That is right.
- But she is not your first love.
- Is she your eighth love?
- No.
- You better not say that to her.
- Fine.
All right. Forget it then.
Yul, you can take my energy.
That is fine.
I was rejected recently.
What?
By whom?
Was it Mu-deok?
No.
The person I had feelings for was not her.
Then who could it have been?
Uk, do you know?
Well, I do have my guesses.
Have you decided on your destination, Uk?
Sari Village. I am curious
about something there as well.
Are you all prepared to go
back to Seoho Fortress?
You are leaving
right after my wedding, right?
I think I will have to go later.
I need more treatment.
Does it still hurt?
I heard the wound had already healed up.
What is this? Is Master Heo a quack?
The wound has healed,
but I still feel some pain.
I will be fine.
Young Master Seo.
I do not know
if I should give this to you.
But a beggar asked me to give this to you.
This medicine
will relieve your chest pain.
You must take it.
This person knows my condition.
Who could it be?
I knew you would come back,
Your Royal Highness.
There is nothing Jang Uk can do,
so I will cast him far away.
As for the ice stone, he does not have it.
Own up to your crimes
by the end of the day.
If you do not,
I will have no choice
but to capture you myself.
You are being deceived by everyone.
Did you meet with Songrim's leader today?
What did he say?
Did he praise you
for being the King's Star?
He is aware that it was Jang Uk, not you.
And so does Master Lee.
Despite that, he barged into the palace
and mentioned the King's Star.
Are you saying that they had
all deceived and mocked me?
They are trying to protect Jang Uk.
The real King's Star has the ice stone,
and Songrim is protecting him.
I am the only one who can protect you,
Your Royal Highness.
He is hiding a great secret.
I will expose him…
and…
make him hit rock bottom.
Darn it.
What? Who drank it all?
Your cup is empty.
It was you, right? You drank it all.
If it is empty, pour me some.
- There we go.
- Have some.
"Have some"? How dare you.
- "Have some"?
- Drink up…
Goodness, it is our young master!
Young Master,
we were having a drink to celebrate
- her resignation from Songrim.
- I see.
- Hi, Jang Uk.
- Hey!
He is our young master.
I am sorry. My mistake.
- That is right.
- They had one too many as well.
Young Master.
Come here.
Let me show you something
really fascinating.
When Mu-deok is drunk,
she does not speak in dialect.
Is that fascinating?
It is a pity
that I cannot show you.
But I can fly up to the roof.
Really? Try it.
- Try it?
- Try it.
Watch closely.
Darn it. Hold on.
- Mu-deok.
- It is not working.
Sit back down.
I cannot do it anymore. I…
I cannot draw that sword either.
What? That?
That is not yours. That was Naksu's.
- Young Master.
- Yes?
Why do you keep bringing
that dreadful thing in here?
I will get rid of it.
Let me try it again.
- Sure. Try it.
- Sit down.
Fly. Do it.
- Wrap up and go to bed.
- Did you see that?
- I will get rid of Mu-deok.
- I can fly.
- Stop moving.
- It worked.
She really did fly.
Leader, did you see that?
I want to fly too.
You kids have no idea who I am.
I am the true master. Want me to show you?
I am the master.
Today is just not my day.
Mu-deok.
Do not drink ever again.
You will tell everyone that you are Naksu.
I have something to tell you.
Sleep now. Tell me tomorrow.
I must say it today.
What if I do nothing and die tomorrow?
Fine, tell me. Since you say you may die.
I am all ears.
Jang Uk.
I like you a lot.
I see. And she went to bed.
Just like that.
I need to tell her what Master Lee said.
I believe Mu-deok's body
originally belonged
to someone with great divine powers.
Maybe I will find out
once I go to Sari Village.
Let bygones be bygones.
You will now become in-laws.
Cho-yeon is not marrying
into the Park family.
Dang-gu is the one marrying into ours.
He is not moving in with your family.
Since you keep saying such things,
people are talking
about how his surname will change to Jin.
Their daughter will be given our surname.
Their son will be given ours.
Do not argue on this wonderful day.
The guests will arrive soon.
You should get ready to greet them.
Go on.
Where is Dang-gu?
He will go
to Sejukwon with Cho-yeon first.
They are going to sneak inside
and greet her father first.
Where is Mu-deok?
I am not sure.
She came here first, but I do not see her.
Is she embarrassed
and avoiding me because of last night?
Naksu.
You cannot draw your sword
because you are stuck in that body.
You are my last weapon.
I will use all my power
to bring out yours.
Once you regain your powers,
you shall run wild.
Only I know who its real owner is.
Your daughter is still alive.
Mother.
Maidservant Kim.
Where did your maid,
Mu-deok, used to live?
Are her parents alive?
No, they are not.
She grew up in Sari Village.
When she was falsely accused
because of that girl, So-i,
I had told you all of this.
I had asked you to help that poor girl.
But you ignored me.
Does So-i know Mu-deok?
Yes. Young Lady Jin also knows her.
You are blindingly beautiful.
You are handsome as well.
Let us go greet your father.
We cannot stay there for long.
If the elders find out,
they will give us an earful.
Right.
Thank you,
my husband.
Be careful,
my wife.
My dear wife.
Wait for me.
Mu-deok? What are you doing here?
Mu-deok, you cannot bring that in here.
First, kill Jin U-tak.
Mu-deok!
What is going on?
Are you not
Jang Uk's maid?
Are you hurt?
Kill Jin U-tak.
Father!
Mu-deok.
What are you doing?
She is…
She is an assassin.
Run, Cho-yeon.
Hurry!
Young Master Park!
Stop Mu-deok.
Mu-deok.
Please stop her!
No…
Kill her. Hurry!
Father!
Do not die!
Father, please…
Father!
Father.
Father, please do not die.
Naksu.
Kill those who murdered your father.
Father!
No!
How dare you show your face here?
Capture that criminal, Jin Mu!
I, Assistant Gwanju Jin Mu,
am here to catch a soul shifter.
Naksu, a soul shifter,
is in Songrim as we speak.
- Naksu?
- My lord!
We have a problem.
An assassin has appeared in Sejukwon.
And that assassin murdered Lord Jin.
That very assassin is Naksu
whom I have been looking for.
That is not true.
It was…
It was Mu-deok.
Mu-deok is Naksu.
An assassin!
An assassin has appeared in Sejukwon!
Get her.
- Go get her!
- Yes, sir!
Mu-deok.
Jang Uk?
Did I do this?
I did.
I stabbed you.
Just one.
I will hold your hand as if it is a ring.
This is a one-of-a-kind ring.
If I become Naksu, I will be in danger.
What happens to me then
will have nothing to do with you.
Why?
Because we will no longer be
master and pupil?
You will no longer
have a reason to protect me.
Nor will I have a reason
to go easy on you.
That was our promise from the start.
Then promise me one more thing.
When you regain your energy
and if you must draw
and point that sword at someone,
point it at me before at anyone else.
If you stab me,
then I will die as the one
who released the assassin.
Jang Uk!
No…
Get her!
Uk…
Uk!
I think…
Uk knew that Mu-deok was Naksu.
Jin Mu
is raiding Jeongjingak
to find proof of that as we speak.
I was aware of it as well.
Please allow me to go find her
and find out what happened.
You are the eldest son of the Seo family.
You did not know anything.
You are forbidden from leaving
the premises from this moment on.
Father died
in the hands of that assassin.
I will find
and kill her.
No.
You must bring her back here alive.
Naksu is only the soul
that is in that body.
I must find out
to whom that body originally belonged.
Bring her back at all costs.
Naksu was the one who performed
the alchemy of souls
alongside the Choi siblings.
I had caught the individual
who had previously escaped
when I had killed all of Naksu's men.
That was how I knew
that Naksu was still alive.
I had been searching for her all along
just to clear my name.
And she was the daughter
of Cho Chung, who was killed
by the four families?
She must have entered Songrim
to avenge her father.
And Jang Gang's son kept her
by his side despite knowing this?
We will never know since he has died.
But I hope you will punish Songrim greatly
for everything that has occurred.
Where is Naksu?
Cheonbugwan's men are after her.
Since she has run wild,
she will soon petrify and meet her demise.
Mu-deok.
Jang Uk!
I am not allowed to wear mourning clothes
nor give him a proper funeral
as if he was a criminal.
How could they burn his body
in such a place?
This cannot happen!
Please stop them…
Songrim…
has no say
in this matter.
I am sorry.
Young Master Jang…
Why am I here?
At least…
I can no longer hear the bells.
Naksu will go to the soul shifters' grave.
That is where she will meet her demise.
You are the King's Star
who has been granted the power of the sky.
This is not your end,
Jang Uk.
Young Master Jang.
A NEW ALCHEMY OF SOULS STORY
WILL BEGIN IN DECEMBER
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim